<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Exceptional Value | iPrepPlus]]></title>
  <link href="http://blog.iprepplus.com//blog/categories/exceptional-value/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://blog.iprepplus.com//"/>
  <updated>2016-03-20T10:30:55-06:00</updated>
  <id>http://blog.iprepplus.com//</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[iPrepPlus]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exceptional Value – Unbelievable Price – Limited Time Offer]]></title>
    <link href="http://blog.iprepplus.com//exceptional-value-unbelievable-price-limited-time-offer/"/>
    <updated>2016-01-13T21:58:56-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://blog.iprepplus.com//exceptional-value-unbelievable-price-limited-time-offer</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="center" src="/images/blog_4.jpg" title="Students" ></p>

<p>For only $60 – about the same price as one hour of face-to-face tutoring – you can get year-long access to electronic study notes and video support for most 30-level subjects!</p>

<!--more-->


<p></p>

<p>How many times have you wanted “just a little extra help” with a tough topic or another way to review your classroom materials?  Now you can!  Each iPrep Plus Electronic Study Notes and Video Support resource package gives you a comprehensive review of your course material and five video support clips to help you improve your understanding of the “tough topics”.  Each video support clip is approximately five to 10 minutes in length – and you can watch it as many times as you want.  Use the resources to help you prepare for class quizzes, assignments, unit tests, and semester exams.</p>

<p>Visit the iPrep Plus web site www.iPrepPlus.com  to check out all of the features for English 30-1, Biology 30, Chemistry 30, Math 30-1, Math 30-2, Physics 30, Science 30, and Social Studies 30-1.  Browse the course content overview.  Watch the “Video Samplers” for each subject.  This is a great offer but it won’t last forever!  Order your resources now!</p>

<p>If you are serious about your academic success – iPrep Plus is here to help you succeed!</p>

<p><strong>iPrep Plus – Home Support for Classroom Learning</strong></p>

<p><em>More than you imagined for less than you expected!</em></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
