<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Study Tips | iPrepPlus]]></title>
  <link href="http://blog.iprepplus.com//blog/categories/study-tips/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://blog.iprepplus.com//"/>
  <updated>2016-04-05T22:17:32-06:00</updated>
  <id>http://blog.iprepplus.com//</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[iPrepPlus]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tell Us What You Think]]></title>
    <link href="http://blog.iprepplus.com//tell-us-what-you-think/"/>
    <updated>2016-03-20T10:16:07-06:00</updated>
    <id>http://blog.iprepplus.com//tell-us-what-you-think</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="center" src="/images/CULTURE1.jpg" title="Students" ></p>

<p>Now that you are responsible for 70% of your final grade, your efforts have a more significant impact on your final results.  <strong>iPrep Plus</strong> is a new offering that provides you with resources you can use at home to support your classroom learning.   We think the combination of electronic study notes and video support provides you with the best opportunity to optimize your learning.  However, we need to hear from you!</p>

<!--more-->


<p></p>

<p>We are interested in knowing what aspects of the resource package worked well for you.  Your feedback will help us to continue to improve our product.  Your testimonial will help to “spread the word” about a unique product designed to help you complete classroom assignments, prepare for unit tests, clarify your understanding, and study for the diploma exams.</p>

<p>Share your comments with us at TESTIMONIALS
<a href="http://iprepplus.com/testimonials">http://iprepplus.com/testimonials</a> or visit the <strong>iPrep Plus</strong> web site www.iPrepPlus.com for more information.  If you are serious about your academic success – <strong>iPrep Plus </strong>is here to help you succeed!</p>

<p><strong>iPrep Plus – Year Long Support for Classroom Learning</strong></p>

<p><em>More than you imagined for less than you expected!</em></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Study Skills Personal Inventory]]></title>
    <link href="http://blog.iprepplus.com//study-skills-personal-inventory/"/>
    <updated>2016-03-14T17:23:08-06:00</updated>
    <id>http://blog.iprepplus.com//study-skills-personal-inventory</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="center" src="/images/learning.jpg" title="Students" ></p>

<p>There is a difference between homework and studying.  Homework is assigned by the teacher and has specific instructions and a “due date”.  Studying is initiated by you – you determine what to study, when and where to do your studying and how long you are going to study the material covered in class.  You can maximize your potential by having a study schedule and knowing where to focus your efforts.</p>

<p>The purpose of this personal inventory is to help you become familiar with your study habits and attitudes.  It is intended to help you identify areas where you may wish to focus on improving your skills.  Read each statement and consider how it applies to you.  Keep track of your responses for each statement.</p>

<!--more-->


<p></p>

<ol>
<li>I feel so overwhelmed with assignments that I can’t get started.<br/>
☐ Yes ☐ No</li>
<li>I usually write my papers at the last minute.<br/>
☐ Yes ☐ No</li>
<li>I have difficulty putting my thoughts on paper.<br/>
☐ Yes ☐ No</li>
<li>When reading I can’t identify the main ideas.<br/>
☐ Yes ☐ No</li>
<li>I use the same reading speed for all subjects and materials.<br/>
☐ Yes ☐ No</li>
<li>I wish I could read faster.<br/>
☐ Yes ☐ No</li>
<li>When I finish a reading assignment, I can’t remember what I’ve just read.<br/>
☐ Yes ☐ No</li>
<li>I find it difficult to determine what is important when reading from a textbook.<br/>
☐ Yes ☐ No</li>
<li>I can’t keep up with my reading assignments, and then I have to cram the night before the exam.<br/>
☐ Yes ☐ No</li>
<li>I spend too much time studying for the amount I am learning.<br/>
☐ Yes ☐ No</li>
<li>I usually cram for an exam.<br/>
☐ Yes ☐ No</li>
<li>Studying interferes with my social life.<br/>
☐ Yes ☐ No</li>
<li>When I study, I turn on the TV or music.<br/>
☐ Yes ☐ No</li>
<li>I find studying for long periods of time very difficult.<br/>
☐ Yes ☐ No</li>
<li>I go to class but I can’t stay focused.<br/>
☐ Yes ☐ No</li>
<li>I don’t understand my class notes.<br/>
☐ Yes ☐ No</li>
<li>My class notes don’t reflect the important material<br/>
☐ Yes ☐ No</li>
<li>I don’t review my class notes when preparing for tests<br/>
☐ Yes ☐ No</li>
<li>I do poorly on essay tests.<br/>
☐ Yes ☐ No</li>
<li>Even when I study for a test, my mind goes blank<br/>
☐ Yes ☐ No</li>
<li>I only study when a test is approaching and don’t do well.<br/>
☐ Yes ☐ No</li>
</ol>


<p>The following chart sorts the questions into categories.  Using your responses to the questions, complete the chart.  The Study Skills Personal Inventory maybe a useful starting point for identifying specific areas that you may wish to focus on to improve of your study habits.  Remember, it is only a starting point.</p>

<h3><strong>Study Skills:</strong>Writing Skills</h3>

<p><strong>Question Numbers: </strong>1, 2, and 3</p>

<p><strong>The number you answered “Yes” to:</strong></p>

<p><strong>Check (✔︎) if you need to focus on this skill:</strong> ☐</p>

<h3><strong>Study Skills:</strong>Reading</h3>

<p><strong>Question Numbers: </strong>4, 5, 6, 7, 8, and 9</p>

<p><strong>The number you answered “Yes” to:</strong></p>

<p><strong>Check (✔︎) if you need to focus on this skill:</strong> ☐</p>

<h3><strong>Study Skills:</strong>Time Scheduling</h3>

<p><strong>Question Numbers: </strong>10, 11, and 12</p>

<p><strong>The number you answered “Yes” to:</strong></p>

<p><strong>Check (✔︎) if you need to focus on this skill:</strong> ☐</p>

<h3><strong>Study Skills:</strong>Concentration</h3>

<p><strong>Question Numbers: </strong>13, 14, and 15</p>

<p><strong>The number you answered “Yes” to:</strong></p>

<p><strong>Check (✔︎) if you need to focus on this skill:</strong> ☐</p>

<h3><strong>Study Skills:</strong>Listening</h3>

<p><strong>Question Numbers: </strong>16, 17, and 18</p>

<p><strong>The number you answered “Yes” to:</strong></p>

<p><strong>Check (✔︎) if you need to focus on this skill:</strong> ☐</p>

<h3><strong>Study Skills:</strong> Exams</h3>

<p><strong>Question Numbers: </strong>19, 20, and 21</p>

<p><strong>The number you answered “Yes” to:</strong></p>

<p><strong>Check (✔︎) if you need to focus on this skill:</strong> ☐</p>

<p>There are many effective strategies that you can learn and apply to help you maximize your study time and improve your achievement.  Like any new skill you learn, you have to practice, practice, practice.  The more you use the skill, the better you become in applying it and the more benefit you get from your study time.</p>

<p>If you are serious about your academic success – iPrep Plus is here to help you succeed!</p>

<p><strong>iPrep Plus – Home Support for Classroom Learning</strong></p>

<p><em>More than you imagined for less than you expected!</em></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
