<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Diplomax]]></title>
  <link href="http://blog.diplomax.ca//atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://blog.diplomax.ca//"/>
  <updated>2016-10-17T21:57:27-06:00</updated>
  <id>http://blog.diplomax.ca//</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Diplomax]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[PRESS RELEASE – PROVINCE-WIDE LAUNCH of DIPLOMAX.CA]]></title>
    <link href="http://blog.diplomax.ca//press-release-province-wide-launch-of-diplomax-dot-ca/"/>
    <updated>2016-10-17T21:21:43-06:00</updated>
    <id>http://blog.diplomax.ca//press-release-province-wide-launch-of-diplomax-dot-ca</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="center" src="http://blog.diplomax.ca//images/DIPLOMAX.CA.png" title="Question" ></p>

<p>Writing any diploma exams this year?  Looking for face-to-face help to prepare for the January or June diplomas?  DIPLOMAX In-Class has it for Edmonton and areas students!  Don’t live close enough to Edmonton to participate?  Don’t worry!  DIPLOMAX On-Line is for you!  It is a comprehensive VIDEO REVIEW that comes with a complimentary copy of the Instructor’s Study Notes.  Looking for something that you can use all year long with class assignments, quizzes and unit tests?  iPrep Plus has just what you are looking for!  Use the electronic study notes with video support for the 10 toughest topics!</p>

<!--more-->


<p></p>

<p><a href="http://www.diplomax.ca">DIPLOMAX.ca</a> is an amazing new service that has the support you need to help you do your best on the diploma exams and your in-class assignments - no matter where you live in Alberta.  As the competition for scholarships and entrance to quota faculties becomes more challenging, it is increasingly important to achieve the highest scores possible on your year-end grades and the provincial diploma exams.  <a href="http://www.diplomax.ca">DIPLOMAX.ca</a> has products and services designed to help you do just that!</p>

<p>Recognizing the need for quality, affordable resources that students can access anytime, anywhere, and on any device, Noel Kunst, noted educator, former assistant superintendent, and now independent consultant, put together a team of experienced and talented instructors to create “what students need” to support their classroom learning and maximize their achievement results.  If you, or anyone you know, is taking Biology 30, Chemistry 30, English 30-1, Math 30-1, Math 30-2, Physics 30, Science 30, or Social 30-1, have them visit www.diplomax.ca to find out more about the new products and services developed especially for them!  Check your school counselling department for printed information about the great products and services available to you through DIPLOMAX.ca!</p>

<p><a href="http://www.diplomax.ca">DIPLOMAX.ca</a>
Year-long Support to Classroom Learning.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[iPrep Plus Gives Students ‘Leg Up’]]></title>
    <link href="http://blog.diplomax.ca//iprep-plus-gives-students-leg-up/"/>
    <updated>2016-05-17T17:42:35-06:00</updated>
    <id>http://blog.diplomax.ca//iprep-plus-gives-students-leg-up</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="center" src="http://blog.diplomax.ca//images/student_edge.jpg" title="Question" ></p>

<p>High-stakes diploma exams in January and June are always a challenge for grade 12 students.   These provincial exams count for 30% of your final grade but the other 70% comes from your efforts on school-based assessments.</p>

<!--more-->


<p></p>

<p>For a variety of reasons, it is becoming more and more common for students to seek assistance beyond the classroom in preparing for the diploma exams.  Entrance requirements for many post-secondary institutions have increased over the years so you need better grades to gain admittance.  The competition is extremely keen for faculties that have quotas and only take the top echelon of applicants.  Then there are the numerous scholarships available for the students who have the top grades!</p>

<p>Teachers work very diligently to get through the extensive, mandated curriculum but often find little time left in the semester for completing a review of the course content.  Students are now looking to external sources for the comprehensive review that will give them the “edge” they need to boost their marks – and open the doors to the future they are seeking.</p>

<p>iPrep Plus gives you exactly what you are looking for! The comprehensive Electronic Study Notes and Video Support resource packages for English 30-1, Biology 30, Chemistry 30, Math 30-1, Math 30-2, Physics 30, Science 30 and Social Studies 30-1 can be used at home to support your classroom learning.  You are provided with a comprehensive course review, video support for the “tough topics”, tips and strategies for writing exams, suggestions for handling exam anxiety, calculator tricks, and effective study hints.</p>

<p>Visit the iPrep Plus web site at www.iPrepPlus.com to watch a “video sampler”, review the course descriptions, and for more information about the introductory price which available for a limited time!</p>

<p>Check out the web site <a href="http://www.iPrepPlus.com">www.iPrepPlus.com</a> for the <strong>introductory price offer</strong> and many features!</p>

<p>If you are serious about your academic success – <strong>iPrep Plus</strong> and <strong>Diplomax</strong> are here to help you!</p>

<p><em>iPrep Plus – Year-long Support for Classroom Learning</em>
More than you imagined for less than you expected – electronic study notes and video support for tough topics!
<a href="http://www.iPrepPlus.com">www.iPrepPlus.com</a></p>

<p><em>Diplomax – Your Premier Choice for Diploma Prep</em>
For Edmonton and area face-to-face review classes in January and June check  <a href="http://www.primetimelearning.ca">www.primetimelearning.ca</a></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Math 30-2 — Sample Question and Solution for Set Theory #3]]></title>
    <link href="http://blog.diplomax.ca//math-30-2-sample-question-and-solution-for-set-theory-number-3/"/>
    <updated>2016-05-15T13:26:04-06:00</updated>
    <id>http://blog.diplomax.ca//math-30-2-sample-question-and-solution-for-set-theory-number-3</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Try this sample question to gauge your diploma preparation for Math 30-2!</p>

<p><img class="center" src="http://blog.diplomax.ca//images/question_SetTheory_1.png" title="Question" ></p>

<!--more-->


<p></p>

<p><img class="center" src="http://blog.diplomax.ca//images/question_SetTheory_2.png" title="Question" ></p>

<p><img class="center" src="http://blog.diplomax.ca//images/question_SetTheory_3.png" title="Question" ></p>

<p>Check out the web site <a href="http://www.iPrepPlus.com">www.iPrepPlus.com</a> for the <strong>introductory price offer</strong> and many features!</p>

<p>If you are serious about your academic success – <strong>iPrep Plus</strong> and <strong>Diplomax</strong> are here to help you!</p>

<p><em>iPrep Plus – Year-long Support for Classroom Learning</em>
More than you imagined for less than you expected – electronic study notes and video support for tough topics!
<a href="http://www.iPrepPlus.com">www.iPrepPlus.com</a></p>

<p><em>Diplomax – Your Premier Choice for Diploma Prep</em>
For Edmonton and area face-to-face review classes in January and June check  <a href="http://www.primetimelearning.ca">www.primetimelearning.ca</a></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Study Schedules – Long-term, Short-term, and PANIC!]]></title>
    <link href="http://blog.diplomax.ca//study-schedules-long-term/"/>
    <updated>2016-05-08T12:17:05-06:00</updated>
    <id>http://blog.diplomax.ca//study-schedules-long-term</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="center" src="http://blog.diplomax.ca//images/grades.jpg" title="&#34;Girls with grades&#34;" alt="&#34;Girls with grades&#34;"></p>

<p>Have you ever read the story of <em>The Hare and the Tortoise?</em>  It is a delightful children’s story of a race between two animal friends who each are confident of their ability to win a race.  The Hare sets off to a speedy start and covers a significant amount of territory before deciding he has enough of a head start on the Tortoise that he can stop for a rest.  He settles under a shady tree and enjoys a nap, confident that he can sprint to the finish line well before the Tortoise can catch up to him.</p>

<!--more-->


<p></p>

<p>The Tortoise leaves the start line slowly plodding along the race path.  Though not a flashy racer, he keeps a steady pace and remains focused on getting to the finish line.  He passes the sleeping Hare and soon sees the finish line looming in the distance.  As the Tortoise is within steps of crossing the finish line and winning the race, the Hare wakes up.  He realizes he needs to make a spirited sprint to overtake the Tortoise.  Unfortunately, the Hare’s panicked dash for the finish line is “too little too late”.  The Tortoise, although a long shot, wins the race and the brazen, confident Hare is left humiliated and searching for an explanation for his loss.</p>

<p>There are many analogies that can be drawn between the race strategies of the story characters and long-term, short-term, and panic study schedules.</p>

<p><strong>Long-term Study Schedules</strong> generally are implemented well in advance of exam time and require you to set aside regular study time on an on-going basis.  Like the Tortoise a slow and steady approach helps to win the race.  The advantage of a long-term study schedule is that once you establish your study routine, it is quite easy to maintain – and shorter, regular periods of study give you the most benefit!</p>

<p><strong>Short-term Study Schedules</strong> are often implemented several days or weeks before an exam and require you to prioritize the time you spend on each topic or concept.  It may be difficult to find a “starting point”.  Do you focus on the things that are most important in the subject or on the concepts that are most challenging to you? Like the Hare, your focus may change before the end of the race.  You may skim over content that you feel you have a firm understanding of in favor of focusing on topics that feel less confident about.  Your focus may not be as consistent or as strong as it needs to be for the duration of your study or exam preparation time. The advantage of a short-term study schedule is that you gain a sense of confidence as you “check off” the topics and concepts you feel confident about.</p>

<p><img class="right" src="http://blog.diplomax.ca//images/panic.jpeg" title="&#34;Panic&#34;" alt="&#34;Panic&#34;"></p>

<p><strong>Panic Study Schedules</strong> usually happen “the night before” the exam – when you realize that you do not have enough time to adequately prepare for your exam.  Although this study schedule requires the least amount of time commitment, it rarely allows you to achieve your potential.  Like the Hare, leaving too much to the end makes it impossible to finish what needs to be done.  However, any effort is better than doing nothing.</p>

<p>To achieve the grades you want requires effort on your part.  A long-term study schedule gives you the best chance for success.  A short-term study schedule may work well in a course where you have a strong understanding of the concepts.  A Panic Study Schedule is better than not studying at all but may not help you to achieve your course goals over the semester or school year.</p>

<p><strong>Does your study strategy resemble the race strategy of the Hare or the Tortoise?</strong></p>

<p>Check out the web site <a href="http://www.iPrepPlus.com">www.iPrepPlus.com</a> for the <strong>introductory price offer</strong> and many features!</p>

<p>If you are serious about your academic success – <strong>iPrep Plus</strong> and <strong>Diplomax</strong> are here to help you!</p>

<p><em>iPrep Plus – Year-long Support for Classroom Learning</em>
More than you imagined for less than you expected – electronic study notes and video support for tough topics!
<a href="http://www.iPrepPlus.com">www.iPrepPlus.com</a></p>

<p><em>Diplomax – Your Premier Choice for Diploma Prep</em>
For Edmonton and area face-to-face review classes in January and June check  <a href="http://www.primetimelearning.ca">www.primetimelearning.ca</a></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Math 30-1 — Sample Question and Solution for Sinusoidal Functions #2]]></title>
    <link href="http://blog.diplomax.ca//math-30-1-sample-question-and-solution-for-sinusoidal-functions-number-2/"/>
    <updated>2016-05-08T11:56:02-06:00</updated>
    <id>http://blog.diplomax.ca//math-30-1-sample-question-and-solution-for-sinusoidal-functions-number-2</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Try this sample question to gauge your diploma preparation for Math 30-1!</p>

<!--more-->


<p></p>

<p><img class="center" src="http://blog.diplomax.ca//images/question2.png" title="Question" ></p>

<p>Check out the web site <a href="http://www.iPrepPlus.com">www.iPrepPlus.com</a> for the <strong>introductory price offer</strong> and many features!</p>

<p>If you are serious about your academic success – <strong>iPrep Plus</strong> and <strong>Diplomax</strong> are here to help you!</p>

<p><em>iPrep Plus – Year-long Support for Classroom Learning</em>
More than you imagined for less than you expected – electronic study notes and video support for tough topics!
<a href="http://www.iPrepPlus.com">www.iPrepPlus.com</a></p>

<p><em>Diplomax – Your Premier Choice for Diploma Prep</em>
For Edmonton and area face-to-face review classes in January and June check  <a href="http://www.primetimelearning.ca">www.primetimelearning.ca</a></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Math 30-1 — Sample Question and Solution for Exponential Functions #1]]></title>
    <link href="http://blog.diplomax.ca//math-30-sample-question-and-solution-number-1/"/>
    <updated>2016-05-03T17:26:03-06:00</updated>
    <id>http://blog.diplomax.ca//math-30-sample-question-and-solution-number-1</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>High-stakes diploma exams in January and June are always a challenge for grade 12 students. These provincial exams count for 30% of a student’s final grade with the other 70% coming from school-based assessments.</p>

<p>For a variety of reasons, it is becoming more and more common for students to seek assistance beyond the classroom in preparing for the diploma exams. Entrance requirements for many post-secondary institutions have increased over the years so students need better grades to gain admittance. The competition is extremely keen for faculties that have quotas and only take the top echelon of applicants. Then there are the numerous scholarships available for the students who have the top grades.</p>

<p>Try this sample question to gauge your diploma preparation for Math 30-1!</p>

<!--more-->


<p></p>

<p><img class="center" src="http://blog.diplomax.ca//images/question1.png" title="Question" ></p>

<p>Check out the web site <a href="http://www.iPrepPlus.com">www.iPrepPlus.com</a> for the <strong>introductory price offer</strong> and many features!</p>

<p>If you are serious about your academic success – <strong>iPrep Plus</strong> and <strong>Diplomax</strong> are here to help you!</p>

<p><em>iPrep Plus – Year-long Support for Classroom Learning</em>
More than you imagined for less than you expected – electronic study notes and video support for tough topics!
<a href="http://www.iPrepPlus.com">www.iPrepPlus.com</a></p>

<p><em>Diplomax – Your Premier Choice for Diploma Prep</em>
For Edmonton and area face-to-face review classes in January and June check  <a href="http://www.primetimelearning.ca">www.primetimelearning.ca</a></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Not Only Authors but Exceptional Educators]]></title>
    <link href="http://blog.diplomax.ca//not-only-authors-but-exceptional-educators/"/>
    <updated>2016-05-02T17:20:34-06:00</updated>
    <id>http://blog.diplomax.ca//not-only-authors-but-exceptional-educators</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="center" src="http://blog.diplomax.ca//images/teacher.jpg" title="Social" ></p>

<p>When there are so many self-help books on the market, how many can you buy, and how do you know which ones will actually be useful?  The answer is easy!  Look for the educational resources that have been developed by experienced educators who have a strong reputation for helping student achieve remarkable results.</p>

<!--more-->


<p></p>

<p>All of the <strong><em>iPrep Plus</em></strong> Electronic Study Notes and Video Support resource packages have been created by actual teachers who understand what students need to know to be successful in the subject.  The <strong><em>iPrep Plus</em></strong> authors have provided a comprehensive overview of the Grade 12 course material in language you can understand, included tips for reviewing, and filmed video support clips on the “tough topics” that seem to present challenges to students.</p>

<p>The veteran educators use their knowledge of curriculum, instruction, assessment, expertise, extensive experiences in developing diploma exam questions and marking provincial exams, and their passion for the subject to create strong resources.  Each Electronic Study Notes and Video Support resource is focused on concepts and skills students need to master to maximize their results!</p>

<p>Many of the authors are provincial nominees and Teacher of Excellence Award winners.  Visit the <strong><em>iPrep Plus</em></strong> web site  <a href="http://www.iPrepPlus.com">www.iPrepPlus.com</a>  and click on Educators’ Bios.  You may even recognize some of these outstanding educators!</p>

<p>Check out the web site <a href="http://www.iPrepPlus.com">www.iPrepPlus.com</a> for the <strong>introductory price offer</strong> and many features!</p>

<p>If you are serious about your academic success – <strong>iPrep Plus</strong> and <strong>Diplomax</strong> are here to help you!</p>

<p><em>iPrep Plus – Year-long Support for Classroom Learning</em>
More than you imagined for less than you expected – electronic study notes and video support for tough topics!
<a href="http://www.iPrepPlus.com">www.iPrepPlus.com</a></p>

<p><em>Diplomax – Your Premier Choice for Diploma Prep</em>
For Edmonton and area face-to-face review classes in January and June check  <a href="http://www.primetimelearning.ca">www.primetimelearning.ca</a></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[iPrep Plus Is Going Social!]]></title>
    <link href="http://blog.diplomax.ca//iprep-plus-is-going-social/"/>
    <updated>2016-04-28T20:40:00-06:00</updated>
    <id>http://blog.diplomax.ca//iprep-plus-is-going-social</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="center" src="http://blog.diplomax.ca//images/Social-media-for-public-relations1.jpg" title="Social" ></p>

<p>Thinking about post-secondary studies?  Trying to qualify for a quota faculty?  Looking at applying for a scholarship?  Worrying about getting your high school diploma? You need to check out the new iPrep Plus Electronic Study Notes and Video Support resource packages
to support your classroom learning!</p>

<!--more-->


<p></p>

<p>Follow iPrep Plus on <a href="https://www.facebook.com/getiPrepPlus/">Facebook</a> and on <a href="https://twitter.com/getiPrepPlus/">Twitter</a>  to get information on:</p>

<ul>
<li>tips and strategies on how to maximize your academic performance</li>
<li>comprehensive Electronic Study Notes and Video Support resource packages for English 30-1, Biology 30, Chemistry 30, Math 30-1, Math 30-2, Physics 30, Science 30, and Social Studies 30-1</li>
<li>techniques for dealing with exam anxiety</li>
<li>practical test writing strategies – including calculator ‘tricks’</li>
<li>strategies for answering multiple choice questions</li>
<li>tips for writing strong thesis statements, essays, and personal responses</li>
<li>comprehension clues to decode meaning</li>
<li>effective study tips</li>
<li>how to prepare for an exam; how to write an exam</li>
</ul>


<p>Check out the web site <a href="http://www.iPrepPlus.com">www.iPrepPlus.com</a> for the <strong>introductory price offer</strong> and many features!</p>

<p>If you are serious about your academic success – <strong>iPrep Plus</strong> and <strong>Diplomax</strong> are here to help you!</p>

<p><em>iPrep Plus – Year-long Support for Classroom Learning</em>
More than you imagined for less than you expected – electronic study notes and video support for tough topics!
<a href="http://www.iPrepPlus.com">www.iPrepPlus.com</a></p>

<p><em>Diplomax – Your Premier Choice for Diploma Prep</em>
For Edmonton and area face-to-face review classes in January and June check  <a href="http://www.primetimelearning.ca">www.primetimelearning.ca</a></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[iPrep Plus (Sequel Solutions Inc.) – SPECIAL OFFER]]></title>
    <link href="http://blog.diplomax.ca//iprep-plus-sequel-solutions-inc-dot-special-offer/"/>
    <updated>2016-04-18T08:20:04-06:00</updated>
    <id>http://blog.diplomax.ca//iprep-plus-sequel-solutions-inc-dot-special-offer</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>PrimeTime Learning and Sequel Solutions Inc. have recently entered into an ‘alliance’ to better serve the educational product/service needs of Grade 12 students in Alberta.</p>

<p><img src="http://blog.diplomax.ca//images/iprem_primetime_2.png" title="iPrepPlus" alt="iPrepPlus" /></p>

<p>To commemorate the alliance, Sequel Solutions Inc. is offering students who purchase four or more iPrep Plus resources a complimentary copy of the 58 page electronic resource ‘Finding Employment’.</p>

<!--more-->


<p></p>

<p>Students who order four or more courses will have ‘Finding Employment’ automatically included in their package of courses.  As with all iPrep Plus resources, ‘Finding Employment’ will need to be saved and/or printed for future use.</p>

<p>In completing the personal analysis found in ‘Finding Employment’ you will have:</p>

<ul>
<li>Identified your personal and professional strengths; become aware of your skills and their alignment with your desired career or job.</li>
<li>Completed a marketplace search for employment opportunities; become familiar with the documentation required in applying for a job and completing a resume.</li>
<li>Reviewed the steps in the interview process; accessed ‘hints’ for making your job interview a ‘success’.</li>
<li>Looked at suggestions for keeping a job; determined what needs to change if you are at first ‘unsuccessful’.</li>
</ul>


<p>Find your ideal summer job, volunteer opportunity – or take steps towards securing a permanent job in your chosen career path!</p>

<p>Check out the web site <a href="http://www.iPrepPlus.com">www.iPrepPlus.com</a> for the <strong>introductory price offer</strong> and many features!</p>

<p>If you are serious about your academic success – <strong>iPrep Plus</strong> and <strong>Diplomax</strong> are here to help you!</p>

<p><em>iPrep Plus – Year-long Support for Classroom Learning</em>
More than you imagined for less than you expected – electronic study notes and video support for tough topics!
<a href="http://www.iPrepPlus.com">www.iPrepPlus.com</a></p>

<p><em>Diplomax – Your Premier Choice for Diploma Prep</em>
For Edmonton and area face-to-face review classes in January and June check  <a href="http://www.primetimelearning.ca">www.primetimelearning.ca</a></p>

<p>Sequel Solutions Inc. (iPrep Plus)
www.iprepplus.com</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Diplomax (PrimeTime Learning) – SPECIAL OFFER]]></title>
    <link href="http://blog.diplomax.ca//diplomax-primetime-learning-special-offer/"/>
    <updated>2016-04-18T08:20:02-06:00</updated>
    <id>http://blog.diplomax.ca//diplomax-primetime-learning-special-offer</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>PrimeTime Learning and Sequel Solutions Inc. have recently entered into an ‘alliance’ to better serve the educational product/service needs of Grade 12 students in Alberta.</p>

<p><img src="http://blog.diplomax.ca//images/iprem_primetime_1.png" title="Diplomax" alt="Diplomax" /></p>

<p>To commemorate the alliance, PrimeTime Learning is offering students who register for three or more Diplomax courses in a semester, an entry into a year-end ‘scholarship draw’.</p>

<!--more-->


<p></p>

<p>Eligible students will be informed by e-mail of their entry into the draw for one of four $250 scholarships.  The draws will take place on June 30th, winners will be contacted, and results reported on the PrimeTime Learning website.</p>

<p>Winning students will have $250 to use in whatever manner they choose.</p>

<ul>
<li>Some will choose to apply the funds to the many costs associated with tuition, or books and materials for their post-secondary education.</li>
<li>Others may choose to apply the funds to costs associated with entering their first career or job.</li>
<li>Still others may decide to ‘reward’ themselves with a summer vacation or trip.</li>
<li>The funds are provided to the winners of the draw with ‘no strings attached’ – please use them in the way you believe is best for you.</li>
</ul>


<p>Check out the web site <a href="http://www.iPrepPlus.com">www.iPrepPlus.com</a> for the <strong>introductory price offer</strong> and many features!</p>

<p>If you are serious about your academic success – <strong>iPrep Plus</strong> and <strong>Diplomax</strong> are here to help you!</p>

<p><em>iPrep Plus – Year-long Support for Classroom Learning</em>
More than you imagined for less than you expected – electronic study notes and video support for tough topics!
<a href="http://www.iPrepPlus.com">www.iPrepPlus.com</a></p>

<p><em>Diplomax – Your Premier Choice for Diploma Prep</em>
For Edmonton and area face-to-face review classes in January and June check  <a href="http://www.primetimelearning.ca">www.primetimelearning.ca</a></p>

<p>Best of luck!
PrimeTime Learning (Diplomax)</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[PRESS RELEASE]]></title>
    <link href="http://blog.diplomax.ca//press-release/"/>
    <updated>2016-04-05T22:14:38-06:00</updated>
    <id>http://blog.diplomax.ca//press-release</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Two of the province&rsquo;s most respected educational companies have recently joined forces - an ALLIANCE designed to provide GRADE 12 STUDENTS with an even STRONGER RANGE of PRODUCTS and SERVICES!</p>

<p><img src="http://blog.diplomax.ca//images/iprem_primetime.png" title="Noel Kunst" alt="Noel Kunst" /></p>

<!--more-->


<p></p>

<p>The unique, complementary services provided by Primetime Learning and iPrep Plus enables Alberta students to access Face-to-Face Diploma Exam Prep, as well as Year-long Study Support at Home.</p>

<p>PrimeTime Learning offers, through Diplomax - 16 hours of review for Diploma exam subjects, in January and June of each year, at the University of Alberta, in Edmonton.</p>

<p>iPrep Plus provides, through electronic Study Notes and Video Support for the &lsquo;tough topics&rsquo;, year-long support to assist in completing homework, preparing for term tests, and reviewing for diploma exams.</p>

<p>To celebrate their expansion of services, each company is offering students a SPECIAL OFFER when ordering multiple courses.  Check out the details on the respective websites.</p>

<p>Check out the web site <a href="http://www.iPrepPlus.com">www.iPrepPlus.com</a> for the <strong>introductory price offer</strong> and many features!</p>

<p>If you are serious about your academic success – <strong>iPrep Plus</strong> and <strong>Diplomax</strong> are here to help you!</p>

<p><em>iPrep Plus – Year-long Support for Classroom Learning</em>
More than you imagined for less than you expected – electronic study notes and video support for tough topics!
<a href="http://www.iPrepPlus.com">www.iPrepPlus.com</a></p>

<p><em>Diplomax – Your Premier Choice for Diploma Prep</em>
For Edmonton and area face-to-face review classes in January and June check  <a href="http://www.primetimelearning.ca">www.primetimelearning.ca</a></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tell Us What You Think]]></title>
    <link href="http://blog.diplomax.ca//tell-us-what-you-think/"/>
    <updated>2016-03-20T10:16:07-06:00</updated>
    <id>http://blog.diplomax.ca//tell-us-what-you-think</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="center" src="http://blog.diplomax.ca//images/CULTURE1.jpg" title="Students" ></p>

<p>Now that you are responsible for 70% of your final grade, your efforts have a more significant impact on your final results.  <strong>iPrep Plus</strong> is a new offering that provides you with resources you can use at home to support your classroom learning.   We think the combination of electronic study notes and video support provides you with the best opportunity to optimize your learning.  However, we need to hear from you!</p>

<!--more-->


<p></p>

<p>We are interested in knowing what aspects of the resource package worked well for you.  Your feedback will help us to continue to improve our product.  Your testimonial will help to “spread the word” about a unique product designed to help you complete classroom assignments, prepare for unit tests, clarify your understanding, and study for the diploma exams.</p>

<p>Share your comments with us at TESTIMONIALS
<a href="http://iprepplus.com/testimonials">http://iprepplus.com/testimonials</a> or visit the <strong>iPrep Plus</strong> web site www.iPrepPlus.com for more information.  If you are serious about your academic success – <strong>iPrep Plus </strong>is here to help you succeed!</p>

<p>Check out the web site <a href="http://www.iPrepPlus.com">www.iPrepPlus.com</a> for the <strong>introductory price offer</strong> and many features!</p>

<p>If you are serious about your academic success – <strong>iPrep Plus</strong> and <strong>Diplomax</strong> are here to help you!</p>

<p><em>iPrep Plus – Year-long Support for Classroom Learning</em>
More than you imagined for less than you expected – electronic study notes and video support for tough topics!
<a href="http://www.iPrepPlus.com">www.iPrepPlus.com</a></p>

<p><em>Diplomax – Your Premier Choice for Diploma Prep</em>
For Edmonton and area face-to-face review classes in January and June check  <a href="http://www.primetimelearning.ca">www.primetimelearning.ca</a></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Study Skills Personal Inventory]]></title>
    <link href="http://blog.diplomax.ca//study-skills-personal-inventory/"/>
    <updated>2016-03-14T17:23:08-06:00</updated>
    <id>http://blog.diplomax.ca//study-skills-personal-inventory</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="center" src="http://blog.diplomax.ca//images/learning.jpg" title="Students" ></p>

<p>There is a difference between homework and studying.  Homework is assigned by the teacher and has specific instructions and a “due date”.  Studying is initiated by you – you determine what to study, when and where to do your studying and how long you are going to study the material covered in class.  You can maximize your potential by having a study schedule and knowing where to focus your efforts.</p>

<p>The purpose of this personal inventory is to help you become familiar with your study habits and attitudes.  It is intended to help you identify areas where you may wish to focus on improving your skills.  Read each statement and consider how it applies to you.  Keep track of your responses for each statement.</p>

<!--more-->


<p></p>

<ol>
<li>I feel so overwhelmed with assignments that I can’t get started.<br/>
☐ Yes ☐ No</li>
<li>I usually write my papers at the last minute.<br/>
☐ Yes ☐ No</li>
<li>I have difficulty putting my thoughts on paper.<br/>
☐ Yes ☐ No</li>
<li>When reading I can’t identify the main ideas.<br/>
☐ Yes ☐ No</li>
<li>I use the same reading speed for all subjects and materials.<br/>
☐ Yes ☐ No</li>
<li>I wish I could read faster.<br/>
☐ Yes ☐ No</li>
<li>When I finish a reading assignment, I can’t remember what I’ve just read.<br/>
☐ Yes ☐ No</li>
<li>I find it difficult to determine what is important when reading from a textbook.<br/>
☐ Yes ☐ No</li>
<li>I can’t keep up with my reading assignments, and then I have to cram the night before the exam.<br/>
☐ Yes ☐ No</li>
<li>I spend too much time studying for the amount I am learning.<br/>
☐ Yes ☐ No</li>
<li>I usually cram for an exam.<br/>
☐ Yes ☐ No</li>
<li>Studying interferes with my social life.<br/>
☐ Yes ☐ No</li>
<li>When I study, I turn on the TV or music.<br/>
☐ Yes ☐ No</li>
<li>I find studying for long periods of time very difficult.<br/>
☐ Yes ☐ No</li>
<li>I go to class but I can’t stay focused.<br/>
☐ Yes ☐ No</li>
<li>I don’t understand my class notes.<br/>
☐ Yes ☐ No</li>
<li>My class notes don’t reflect the important material<br/>
☐ Yes ☐ No</li>
<li>I don’t review my class notes when preparing for tests<br/>
☐ Yes ☐ No</li>
<li>I do poorly on essay tests.<br/>
☐ Yes ☐ No</li>
<li>Even when I study for a test, my mind goes blank<br/>
☐ Yes ☐ No</li>
<li>I only study when a test is approaching and don’t do well.<br/>
☐ Yes ☐ No</li>
</ol>


<p>The following chart sorts the questions into categories.  Using your responses to the questions, complete the chart.  The Study Skills Personal Inventory maybe a useful starting point for identifying specific areas that you may wish to focus on to improve of your study habits.  Remember, it is only a starting point.</p>

<h3><strong>Study Skills:</strong>Writing Skills</h3>

<p><strong>Question Numbers: </strong>1, 2, and 3</p>

<p><strong>The number you answered “Yes” to:</strong></p>

<p><strong>Check (✔︎) if you need to focus on this skill:</strong> ☐</p>

<h3><strong>Study Skills:</strong>Reading</h3>

<p><strong>Question Numbers: </strong>4, 5, 6, 7, 8, and 9</p>

<p><strong>The number you answered “Yes” to:</strong></p>

<p><strong>Check (✔︎) if you need to focus on this skill:</strong> ☐</p>

<h3><strong>Study Skills:</strong>Time Scheduling</h3>

<p><strong>Question Numbers: </strong>10, 11, and 12</p>

<p><strong>The number you answered “Yes” to:</strong></p>

<p><strong>Check (✔︎) if you need to focus on this skill:</strong> ☐</p>

<h3><strong>Study Skills:</strong>Concentration</h3>

<p><strong>Question Numbers: </strong>13, 14, and 15</p>

<p><strong>The number you answered “Yes” to:</strong></p>

<p><strong>Check (✔︎) if you need to focus on this skill:</strong> ☐</p>

<h3><strong>Study Skills:</strong>Listening</h3>

<p><strong>Question Numbers: </strong>16, 17, and 18</p>

<p><strong>The number you answered “Yes” to:</strong></p>

<p><strong>Check (✔︎) if you need to focus on this skill:</strong> ☐</p>

<h3><strong>Study Skills:</strong> Exams</h3>

<p><strong>Question Numbers: </strong>19, 20, and 21</p>

<p><strong>The number you answered “Yes” to:</strong></p>

<p><strong>Check (✔︎) if you need to focus on this skill:</strong> ☐</p>

<p>There are many effective strategies that you can learn and apply to help you maximize your study time and improve your achievement.  Like any new skill you learn, you have to practice, practice, practice.  The more you use the skill, the better you become in applying it and the more benefit you get from your study time.</p>

<p>If you are serious about your academic success – iPrep Plus is here to help you succeed!</p>

<p>Check out the web site <a href="http://www.iPrepPlus.com">www.iPrepPlus.com</a> for the <strong>introductory price offer</strong> and many features!</p>

<p>If you are serious about your academic success – <strong>iPrep Plus</strong> and <strong>Diplomax</strong> are here to help you!</p>

<p><em>iPrep Plus – Year-long Support for Classroom Learning</em>
More than you imagined for less than you expected – electronic study notes and video support for tough topics!
<a href="http://www.iPrepPlus.com">www.iPrepPlus.com</a></p>

<p><em>Diplomax – Your Premier Choice for Diploma Prep</em>
For Edmonton and area face-to-face review classes in January and June check  <a href="http://www.primetimelearning.ca">www.primetimelearning.ca</a></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exceptional Value – Unbelievable Price – Limited Time Offer]]></title>
    <link href="http://blog.diplomax.ca//exceptional-value-unbelievable-price-limited-time-offer/"/>
    <updated>2016-01-13T21:58:56-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://blog.diplomax.ca//exceptional-value-unbelievable-price-limited-time-offer</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="center" src="http://blog.diplomax.ca//images/blog_4.jpg" title="Students" ></p>

<p>For only $60 – about the same price as one hour of face-to-face tutoring – you can get year-long access to electronic study notes and video support for most 30-level subjects!</p>

<!--more-->


<p></p>

<p>How many times have you wanted “just a little extra help” with a tough topic or another way to review your classroom materials?  Now you can!  Each iPrep Plus Electronic Study Notes and Video Support resource package gives you a comprehensive review of your course material and five video support clips to help you improve your understanding of the “tough topics”.  Each video support clip is approximately five to 10 minutes in length – and you can watch it as many times as you want.  Use the resources to help you prepare for class quizzes, assignments, unit tests, and semester exams.</p>

<p>Visit the iPrep Plus web site www.iPrepPlus.com  to check out all of the features for English 30-1, Biology 30, Chemistry 30, Math 30-1, Math 30-2, Physics 30, Science 30, and Social Studies 30-1.  Browse the course content overview.  Watch the “Video Samplers” for each subject.  This is a great offer but it won’t last forever!  Order your resources now!</p>

<p>Check out the web site <a href="http://www.iPrepPlus.com">www.iPrepPlus.com</a> for the <strong>introductory price offer</strong> and many features!</p>

<p>If you are serious about your academic success – <strong>iPrep Plus</strong> and <strong>Diplomax</strong> are here to help you!</p>

<p><em>iPrep Plus – Year-long Support for Classroom Learning</em>
More than you imagined for less than you expected – electronic study notes and video support for tough topics!
<a href="http://www.iPrepPlus.com">www.iPrepPlus.com</a></p>

<p><em>Diplomax – Your Premier Choice for Diploma Prep</em>
For Edmonton and area face-to-face review classes in January and June check  <a href="http://www.primetimelearning.ca">www.primetimelearning.ca</a></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Global Citizens]]></title>
    <link href="http://blog.diplomax.ca//global-citizens/"/>
    <updated>2016-01-01T09:30:15-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://blog.diplomax.ca//global-citizens</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="center" src="http://blog.diplomax.ca//images/global-citizen-img1.jpg" title="Bali Students" ></p>

<p>Technology has changed our world making it a global community – but not all citizens in this global community have access to the same educational opportunities to make their life better.  In a developed country, education is perceived as a “right” and not often valued, but in a third-world country education is seen as a “privilege” for those very few who can afford it.  This is definitely the case in the island of Bali, Indonesia.</p>

<!--more-->


<p></p>

<p><img class="right" src="http://blog.diplomax.ca//images/global-citizen-img2.jpg" width="400" title="Bali Students" ></p>

<p>East Bali is the poorest part of the island where the average income is $100 per month – or about $3 a day.  Think about trying to support a family of six or more on $3 a day!  Although the Indonesian government provides free education in its government run schools, there are not schools in every village.  Families must pay for school supplies, transportation and at least three school uniforms for each child before a child can attend school.  It is no surprise that not all children – even from the same family –  can go to school when families are struggling to buy rice to eat, clothing for their family, and provide some sort of living accommodation.  Education is viewed as the ultimate privilege and certain pathway to a better life.</p>

<p><img class="left" src="http://blog.diplomax.ca//images/global-citizen-img3.jpg" width="400" title="Bali Students" ></p>

<p>In a global community we are all responsible for the well-being of each other.  Sequel Solutions Inc., through the sale of iPrep Plus Electronic Study Notes and Video Support resource packages, pledges to provide on-going financial support to enhance the educational opportunities for the children in East Bali.   The financial support goes to provide free after school and weekend classes for all children.  The Balinese teacher is provided and there is no cost to the families for the educational supplies and materials.  Children learn basic English, enhance their Math skills, practice reading and writing, and enjoy some cultural activities.</p>

<p>Visit Global Citizens (<a href="http://iprepplus.com/Global-Citizens">http://iprepplus.com/Global-Citizens</a>) on the iPrep Plus web site for photos and more information on what has already been accomplished.  Together we can make a difference!</p>

<p>Check out the web site <a href="http://www.iPrepPlus.com">www.iPrepPlus.com</a> for the <strong>introductory price offer</strong> and many features!</p>

<p>If you are serious about your academic success – <strong>iPrep Plus</strong> and <strong>Diplomax</strong> are here to help you!</p>

<p><em>iPrep Plus – Year-long Support for Classroom Learning</em>
More than you imagined for less than you expected – electronic study notes and video support for tough topics!
<a href="http://www.iPrepPlus.com">www.iPrepPlus.com</a></p>

<p><em>Diplomax – Your Premier Choice for Diploma Prep</em>
For Edmonton and area face-to-face review classes in January and June check  <a href="http://www.primetimelearning.ca">www.primetimelearning.ca</a></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is iPrepPlus?]]></title>
    <link href="http://blog.diplomax.ca//what-is-iprepplus/"/>
    <updated>2015-12-20T18:00:00-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://blog.diplomax.ca//what-is-iprepplus</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><strong>iPrep Plus</strong> is a unique home support to classroom learning for English 30-1, Biology 30, Chemistry 30, Math 30-1, Math 30-2, Physics 30, Science 30, and Social 30 -1.  Each resource package consists of electronic review notes of 50-150 pages and support videos, each 5-10 minutes in length.  <strong>iPrep Plus</strong> electronic resource packages can be accessed anytime, anywhere and on any device!</p>

<p><img src="http://blog.diplomax.ca//images/shutterstock_64648132.jpg" title="Noel Kunst" alt="Student Studying" /></p>

<!--more-->


<p></p>

<p>All of the electronic resource packages have been developed by well-respected teachers with a reputation for excellence in teaching and achieving exceptional results with students in the classroom and on diploma examinations.</p>

<p><strong>iPrep Plus</strong> provides you with a complete, structured, and comprehensive review of course material and short video clips to help you understand some of the most challenging concepts of a course.  For approximately the same cost as one hour of face-to-face tutoring, you can have <em>unlimited</em> access to the resources for one <strong>iPrep Plus</strong> subject.  You and your school are responsible for 70% of your final grade – maximize your potential!  Use the materials at home to support your course review, class assignments, and exam preparation.</p>

<p>Check out the web site <a href="http://www.iPrepPlus.com">www.iPrepPlus.com</a> for the <strong>introductory price offer</strong> and many features!</p>

<p>If you are serious about your academic success – <strong>iPrep Plus</strong> and <strong>Diplomax</strong> are here to help you!</p>

<p><em>iPrep Plus – Year-long Support for Classroom Learning</em>
More than you imagined for less than you expected – electronic study notes and video support for tough topics!
<a href="http://www.iPrepPlus.com">www.iPrepPlus.com</a></p>

<p><em>Diplomax – Your Premier Choice for Diploma Prep</em>
For Edmonton and area face-to-face review classes in January and June check  <a href="http://www.primetimelearning.ca">www.primetimelearning.ca</a></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[PRESS RELEASE <br/>DIPLOMAX Co-founder Launches New Service – iPREP PLUS]]></title>
    <link href="http://blog.diplomax.ca//press-release/"/>
    <updated>2015-10-20T19:21:38-06:00</updated>
    <id>http://blog.diplomax.ca//press-release</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>DIPLOMAX co-founder Noel Kunst is pleased to announce the launch of <strong>iPrep Plus – Home Support to Classroom Learning</strong>.  It is a province-wide, complementary service to the popular face-to-face review sessions of DIPLOMAX which are held twice a year in Edmonton to assist students in preparing for the provincial diploma exams.</p>

<p><img src="http://blog.diplomax.ca//images/Noel_Kunst_4935_colour.jpg" title="Noel Kunst" alt="Noel Kunst" /></p>

<!--more-->


<p></p>

<p>iPrep Plus provides students with <strong>unlimited access</strong> to an <strong>electronic Study Notes</strong> package and <strong>Video Support</strong> for the “tough topics” in English 30-1, Social Studies 30-1, Biology 30, Chemistry 30, Math 30-1, Math 30-2, Physics 30, and Science 30.  The resources can be used anytime, on any device, anywhere to support students in their day-to-day studies, class assignments, quizzes and unit or final tests.  Now that 70% of final grades are assigned by the school, it is more important than ever that students have access to quality materials to support their home study.</p>

<p>The <strong>electronic Study Notes</strong> of 50-150 pages provides a focused and comprehensive review of all course content.  The <strong>Video Support</strong>, comprised of five to ten minutes videos, deals with the “tough topics” of the course identifying common problems or errors students make, and providing a summary of helpful suggestions and hints to overcome and master the challenges.  The best news about <em>iPrep Plus</em> is that students can have <strong>immediate and unlimited access</strong> to all this for <strong>the same cost as one hour of traditional tutoring</strong>!!</p>

<p>Check out the web site <a href="http://www.iPrepPlus.com">www.iPrepPlus.com</a> for the <strong>introductory price offer</strong> and many features!</p>

<p>If you are serious about your academic success – <strong>iPrep Plus</strong> and <strong>Diplomax</strong> are here to help you!</p>

<p><em>iPrep Plus – Year-long Support for Classroom Learning</em>
More than you imagined for less than you expected – electronic study notes and video support for tough topics!
<a href="http://www.iPrepPlus.com">www.iPrepPlus.com</a></p>

<p><em>Diplomax – Your Premier Choice for Diploma Prep</em>
For Edmonton and area face-to-face review classes in January and June check  <a href="http://www.primetimelearning.ca">www.primetimelearning.ca</a></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
