<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[iPrepPlus]]></title>
  <link href="http://blog.iprepplus.com//atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://blog.iprepplus.com//"/>
  <updated>2016-04-05T22:21:46-06:00</updated>
  <id>http://blog.iprepplus.com//</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[iPrepPlus]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[PRESS RELEASE]]></title>
    <link href="http://blog.iprepplus.com//press-release/"/>
    <updated>2016-04-05T22:14:38-06:00</updated>
    <id>http://blog.iprepplus.com//press-release</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Two of the province&rsquo;s most respected educational companies have recently joined forces - an ALLIANCE designed to provide GRADE 12 STUDENTS with an even STRONGER RANGE of PRODUCTS and SERVICES!</p>

<p><img src="http://blog.iprepplus.com//images/Noel_Kunst_4935_colour.jpg" title="Noel Kunst" alt="Noel Kunst" /></p>

<!--more-->


<p></p>

<p>The unique, complementary services provided by Primetime Learning and iPrep Plus enables Alberta students to access Face-to-Face Diploma Exam Prep, as well as Year-long Study Support at Home.</p>

<p>PrimeTime Learning offers, through Diplomax - 16 hours of review for Diploma exam subjects, in January and June of each year, at the University of Alberta, in Edmonton.</p>

<p>iPrep Plus provides, through electronic Study Notes and Video Support for the &lsquo;tough topics&rsquo;, year-long support to assist in completing homework, preparing for term tests, and reviewing for diploma exams.</p>

<p>To celebrate their expansion of services, each company is offering students a SPECIAL OFFER when ordering multiple courses.  Check out the details on the respective websites.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tell Us What You Think]]></title>
    <link href="http://blog.iprepplus.com//tell-us-what-you-think/"/>
    <updated>2016-03-20T10:16:07-06:00</updated>
    <id>http://blog.iprepplus.com//tell-us-what-you-think</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="center" src="http://blog.iprepplus.com//images/CULTURE1.jpg" title="Students" ></p>

<p>Now that you are responsible for 70% of your final grade, your efforts have a more significant impact on your final results.  <strong>iPrep Plus</strong> is a new offering that provides you with resources you can use at home to support your classroom learning.   We think the combination of electronic study notes and video support provides you with the best opportunity to optimize your learning.  However, we need to hear from you!</p>

<!--more-->


<p></p>

<p>We are interested in knowing what aspects of the resource package worked well for you.  Your feedback will help us to continue to improve our product.  Your testimonial will help to “spread the word” about a unique product designed to help you complete classroom assignments, prepare for unit tests, clarify your understanding, and study for the diploma exams.</p>

<p>Share your comments with us at TESTIMONIALS
<a href="http://iprepplus.com/testimonials">http://iprepplus.com/testimonials</a> or visit the <strong>iPrep Plus</strong> web site www.iPrepPlus.com for more information.  If you are serious about your academic success – <strong>iPrep Plus </strong>is here to help you succeed!</p>

<p><strong>iPrep Plus – Year Long Support for Classroom Learning</strong></p>

<p><em>More than you imagined for less than you expected!</em></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Study Skills Personal Inventory]]></title>
    <link href="http://blog.iprepplus.com//study-skills-personal-inventory/"/>
    <updated>2016-03-14T17:23:08-06:00</updated>
    <id>http://blog.iprepplus.com//study-skills-personal-inventory</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="center" src="http://blog.iprepplus.com//images/learning.jpg" title="Students" ></p>

<p>There is a difference between homework and studying.  Homework is assigned by the teacher and has specific instructions and a “due date”.  Studying is initiated by you – you determine what to study, when and where to do your studying and how long you are going to study the material covered in class.  You can maximize your potential by having a study schedule and knowing where to focus your efforts.</p>

<p>The purpose of this personal inventory is to help you become familiar with your study habits and attitudes.  It is intended to help you identify areas where you may wish to focus on improving your skills.  Read each statement and consider how it applies to you.  Keep track of your responses for each statement.</p>

<!--more-->


<p></p>

<ol>
<li>I feel so overwhelmed with assignments that I can’t get started.<br/>
☐ Yes ☐ No</li>
<li>I usually write my papers at the last minute.<br/>
☐ Yes ☐ No</li>
<li>I have difficulty putting my thoughts on paper.<br/>
☐ Yes ☐ No</li>
<li>When reading I can’t identify the main ideas.<br/>
☐ Yes ☐ No</li>
<li>I use the same reading speed for all subjects and materials.<br/>
☐ Yes ☐ No</li>
<li>I wish I could read faster.<br/>
☐ Yes ☐ No</li>
<li>When I finish a reading assignment, I can’t remember what I’ve just read.<br/>
☐ Yes ☐ No</li>
<li>I find it difficult to determine what is important when reading from a textbook.<br/>
☐ Yes ☐ No</li>
<li>I can’t keep up with my reading assignments, and then I have to cram the night before the exam.<br/>
☐ Yes ☐ No</li>
<li>I spend too much time studying for the amount I am learning.<br/>
☐ Yes ☐ No</li>
<li>I usually cram for an exam.<br/>
☐ Yes ☐ No</li>
<li>Studying interferes with my social life.<br/>
☐ Yes ☐ No</li>
<li>When I study, I turn on the TV or music.<br/>
☐ Yes ☐ No</li>
<li>I find studying for long periods of time very difficult.<br/>
☐ Yes ☐ No</li>
<li>I go to class but I can’t stay focused.<br/>
☐ Yes ☐ No</li>
<li>I don’t understand my class notes.<br/>
☐ Yes ☐ No</li>
<li>My class notes don’t reflect the important material<br/>
☐ Yes ☐ No</li>
<li>I don’t review my class notes when preparing for tests<br/>
☐ Yes ☐ No</li>
<li>I do poorly on essay tests.<br/>
☐ Yes ☐ No</li>
<li>Even when I study for a test, my mind goes blank<br/>
☐ Yes ☐ No</li>
<li>I only study when a test is approaching and don’t do well.<br/>
☐ Yes ☐ No</li>
</ol>


<p>The following chart sorts the questions into categories.  Using your responses to the questions, complete the chart.  The Study Skills Personal Inventory maybe a useful starting point for identifying specific areas that you may wish to focus on to improve of your study habits.  Remember, it is only a starting point.</p>

<h3><strong>Study Skills:</strong>Writing Skills</h3>

<p><strong>Question Numbers: </strong>1, 2, and 3</p>

<p><strong>The number you answered “Yes” to:</strong></p>

<p><strong>Check (✔︎) if you need to focus on this skill:</strong> ☐</p>

<h3><strong>Study Skills:</strong>Reading</h3>

<p><strong>Question Numbers: </strong>4, 5, 6, 7, 8, and 9</p>

<p><strong>The number you answered “Yes” to:</strong></p>

<p><strong>Check (✔︎) if you need to focus on this skill:</strong> ☐</p>

<h3><strong>Study Skills:</strong>Time Scheduling</h3>

<p><strong>Question Numbers: </strong>10, 11, and 12</p>

<p><strong>The number you answered “Yes” to:</strong></p>

<p><strong>Check (✔︎) if you need to focus on this skill:</strong> ☐</p>

<h3><strong>Study Skills:</strong>Concentration</h3>

<p><strong>Question Numbers: </strong>13, 14, and 15</p>

<p><strong>The number you answered “Yes” to:</strong></p>

<p><strong>Check (✔︎) if you need to focus on this skill:</strong> ☐</p>

<h3><strong>Study Skills:</strong>Listening</h3>

<p><strong>Question Numbers: </strong>16, 17, and 18</p>

<p><strong>The number you answered “Yes” to:</strong></p>

<p><strong>Check (✔︎) if you need to focus on this skill:</strong> ☐</p>

<h3><strong>Study Skills:</strong> Exams</h3>

<p><strong>Question Numbers: </strong>19, 20, and 21</p>

<p><strong>The number you answered “Yes” to:</strong></p>

<p><strong>Check (✔︎) if you need to focus on this skill:</strong> ☐</p>

<p>There are many effective strategies that you can learn and apply to help you maximize your study time and improve your achievement.  Like any new skill you learn, you have to practice, practice, practice.  The more you use the skill, the better you become in applying it and the more benefit you get from your study time.</p>

<p>If you are serious about your academic success – iPrep Plus is here to help you succeed!</p>

<p><strong>iPrep Plus – Home Support for Classroom Learning</strong></p>

<p><em>More than you imagined for less than you expected!</em></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exceptional Value – Unbelievable Price – Limited Time Offer]]></title>
    <link href="http://blog.iprepplus.com//exceptional-value-unbelievable-price-limited-time-offer/"/>
    <updated>2016-01-13T21:58:56-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://blog.iprepplus.com//exceptional-value-unbelievable-price-limited-time-offer</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="center" src="http://blog.iprepplus.com//images/blog_4.jpg" title="Students" ></p>

<p>For only $60 – about the same price as one hour of face-to-face tutoring – you can get year-long access to electronic study notes and video support for most 30-level subjects!</p>

<!--more-->


<p></p>

<p>How many times have you wanted “just a little extra help” with a tough topic or another way to review your classroom materials?  Now you can!  Each iPrep Plus Electronic Study Notes and Video Support resource package gives you a comprehensive review of your course material and five video support clips to help you improve your understanding of the “tough topics”.  Each video support clip is approximately five to 10 minutes in length – and you can watch it as many times as you want.  Use the resources to help you prepare for class quizzes, assignments, unit tests, and semester exams.</p>

<p>Visit the iPrep Plus web site www.iPrepPlus.com  to check out all of the features for English 30-1, Biology 30, Chemistry 30, Math 30-1, Math 30-2, Physics 30, Science 30, and Social Studies 30-1.  Browse the course content overview.  Watch the “Video Samplers” for each subject.  This is a great offer but it won’t last forever!  Order your resources now!</p>

<p>If you are serious about your academic success – iPrep Plus is here to help you succeed!</p>

<p><strong>iPrep Plus – Home Support for Classroom Learning</strong></p>

<p><em>More than you imagined for less than you expected!</em></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Global Citizens]]></title>
    <link href="http://blog.iprepplus.com//global-citizens/"/>
    <updated>2016-01-01T09:30:15-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://blog.iprepplus.com//global-citizens</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="center" src="http://blog.iprepplus.com//images/global-citizen-img1.jpg" title="Bali Students" ></p>

<p>Technology has changed our world making it a global community – but not all citizens in this global community have access to the same educational opportunities to make their life better.  In a developed country, education is perceived as a “right” and not often valued, but in a third-world country education is seen as a “privilege” for those very few who can afford it.  This is definitely the case in the island of Bali, Indonesia.</p>

<!--more-->


<p></p>

<p><img class="right" src="http://blog.iprepplus.com//images/global-citizen-img2.jpg" width="400" title="Bali Students" ></p>

<p>East Bali is the poorest part of the island where the average income is $100 per month – or about $3 a day.  Think about trying to support a family of six or more on $3 a day!  Although the Indonesian government provides free education in its government run schools, there are not schools in every village.  Families must pay for school supplies, transportation and at least three school uniforms for each child before a child can attend school.  It is no surprise that not all children – even from the same family –  can go to school when families are struggling to buy rice to eat, clothing for their family, and provide some sort of living accommodation.  Education is viewed as the ultimate privilege and certain pathway to a better life.</p>

<p><img class="left" src="http://blog.iprepplus.com//images/global-citizen-img3.jpg" width="400" title="Bali Students" ></p>

<p>In a global community we are all responsible for the well-being of each other.  Sequel Solutions Inc., through the sale of iPrep Plus Electronic Study Notes and Video Support resource packages, pledges to provide on-going financial support to enhance the educational opportunities for the children in East Bali.   The financial support goes to provide free after school and weekend classes for all children.  The Balinese teacher is provided and there is no cost to the families for the educational supplies and materials.  Children learn basic English, enhance their Math skills, practice reading and writing, and enjoy some cultural activities.</p>

<p>Visit Global Citizens (<a href="http://iprepplus.com/Global-Citizens">http://iprepplus.com/Global-Citizens</a>) on the iPrep Plus web site for photos and more information on what has already been accomplished.  Together we can make a difference!</p>

<p>If you are serious about your academic success – iPrep Plus is here to help you succeed!</p>

<p><strong>iPrep Plus – Home Support for Classroom Learning</strong>
<em>More than you imagined for less than you expected!</em></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is iPrepPlus?]]></title>
    <link href="http://blog.iprepplus.com//what-is-iprepplus/"/>
    <updated>2015-12-20T18:00:00-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://blog.iprepplus.com//what-is-iprepplus</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><strong>iPrep Plus</strong> is a unique home support to classroom learning for English 30-1, Biology 30, Chemistry 30, Math 30-1, Math 30-2, Physics 30, Science 30, and Social 30 -1.  Each resource package consists of electronic review notes of 50-150 pages and support videos, each 5-10 minutes in length.  <strong>iPrep Plus</strong> electronic resource packages can be accessed anytime, anywhere and on any device!</p>

<p><img src="http://blog.iprepplus.com//images/shutterstock_64648132.jpg" title="Noel Kunst" alt="Student Studying" /></p>

<!--more-->


<p></p>

<p>All of the electronic resource packages have been developed by well-respected teachers with a reputation for excellence in teaching and achieving exceptional results with students in the classroom and on diploma examinations.</p>

<p><strong>iPrep Plus</strong> provides you with a complete, structured, and comprehensive review of course material and short video clips to help you understand some of the most challenging concepts of a course.  For approximately the same cost as one hour of face-to-face tutoring, you can have <em>unlimited</em> access to the resources for one <strong>iPrep Plus</strong> subject.  You and your school are responsible for 70% of your final grade – maximize your potential!  Use the materials at home to support your course review, class assignments, and exam preparation.</p>

<p>Visit the <strong>iPrep Plus</strong> web site <a href="http://www.iPrepPlus.com">www.iPrepPlus.com</a> for information and introductory pricing. If you are serious about your academic success – iPrep Plus is here to help you succeed!</p>

<p><strong>iPrep Plus – Home Support for Classroom Learning</strong>
<em>More than you imagined for less than you expected!</em></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[PRESS RELEASE <br/>DIPLOMAX Co-founder Launches New Service – iPREP PLUS]]></title>
    <link href="http://blog.iprepplus.com//press-release/"/>
    <updated>2015-10-20T19:21:38-06:00</updated>
    <id>http://blog.iprepplus.com//press-release</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>DIPLOMAX co-founder Noel Kunst is pleased to announce the launch of <strong>iPrep Plus – Home Support to Classroom Learning</strong>.  It is a province-wide, complementary service to the popular face-to-face review sessions of DIPLOMAX which are held twice a year in Edmonton to assist students in preparing for the provincial diploma exams.</p>

<p><img src="http://blog.iprepplus.com//images/Noel_Kunst_4935_colour.jpg" title="Noel Kunst" alt="Noel Kunst" /></p>

<!--more-->


<p></p>

<p>iPrep Plus provides students with <strong>unlimited access</strong> to an <strong>electronic Study Notes</strong> package and <strong>Video Support</strong> for the “tough topics” in English 30-1, Social Studies 30-1, Biology 30, Chemistry 30, Math 30-1, Math 30-2, Physics 30, and Science 30.  The resources can be used anytime, on any device, anywhere to support students in their day-to-day studies, class assignments, quizzes and unit or final tests.  Now that 70% of final grades are assigned by the school, it is more important than ever that students have access to quality materials to support their home study.</p>

<p>The <strong>electronic Study Notes</strong> of 50-150 pages provides a focused and comprehensive review of all course content.  The <strong>Video Support</strong>, comprised of five to ten minutes videos, deals with the “tough topics” of the course identifying common problems or errors students make, and providing a summary of helpful suggestions and hints to overcome and master the challenges.  The best news about <em>iPrep Plus</em> is that students can have <strong>immediate and unlimited access</strong> to all this for <strong>the same cost as one hour of traditional tutoring</strong>!!</p>

<p>Check out the web site <a href="http://www.iPrepPlus.com">www.iPrepPlus.com</a> for the <strong>introductory price offer</strong> and many features!</p>

<p><strong>iPrep Plus – Home Support for Classroom Learning
More than you imagined for less than you expected!</strong></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
