<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Diplomax]]></title>
  <link href="http://blog.diplomax.ca//atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://blog.diplomax.ca//"/>
  <updated>2018-05-12T11:38:54-06:00</updated>
  <id>http://blog.diplomax.ca//</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Diplomax]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Diploma Prep Study Options]]></title>
    <link href="http://blog.diplomax.ca//diploma-prep-study-options/"/>
    <updated>2018-05-07T19:26:47-06:00</updated>
    <id>http://blog.diplomax.ca//diploma-prep-study-options</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="center" src="http://blog.diplomax.ca//images/blog_4.jpg" title="teacher" ></p>

<p>The new semester is now underway!  We are pleased to remind you that <strong><a href="http://www.diplomax.ca">DIPLOMAX.ca</a></strong>  is now accepting registrations for the June <strong>DIPLOMAX In-Class</strong> sessions.  Check out the schedule and register early to secure a spot in the class and session of your choice. Remember – as soon as you complete your registration, you can immediately start to use the Instructor’s Study Notes package to support your classroom instruction.</p>

<!--more-->


<p>If you are not able to attend the <strong><a href="http://www.diplomax.ca">DIPLOMAX</a></strong>  In-Class sessions, check out the DIPLOMAX On-Line sessions and the <strong>iPrep Plus Electronic Study Notes and Video Support</strong> resources.  <strong>DIPLOMAX On-Line</strong> provides you with a complete video review of the course content – just like the <strong><a href="http://www.diplomax.ca">DIPLOMAX</a></strong>  In-Class session.  And, you receive a complimentary copy of the Instructor’s Study Notes to download or print.  It’s like being at the session only you can access the video review whenever you want and replay the instruction as many times as you want.  There is no need to download the video review.  You can stream the review on any of your devices.</p>

<p>The <strong>iPrep Plus Electronic Study Notes and Video Support</strong> resources offer you a completely different form of course review than either the DIPLOMAX In-Class or On-Line course review.  The Electronic Study Notes are color-coded to provide you with hints and reminders about various topics and strategies as you work your way through the subject material.  There are 10, short, 8-10 minute videos which focus on the most challenging concepts in each course.  Between the study notes and the videos, you have a very comprehensive review package!</p>

<p>Check out the 3-course semester bundle!  It’s an economical way to help you prepare for your diploma exams whether you are writing them in January, April, June, August or November.</p>

<p><a href="http://www.diplomax.ca">DIPLOMAX.ca</a>
Year-long Support to Classroom Learning.</p>

<p><strong>Not only Authors BUT Exceptional Educators</strong></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Not Only Authors but Exceptional Educators]]></title>
    <link href="http://blog.diplomax.ca//not-only-authors-but-exceptional-educators/"/>
    <updated>2017-05-23T18:45:58-06:00</updated>
    <id>http://blog.diplomax.ca//not-only-authors-but-exceptional-educators</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="center" src="http://blog.diplomax.ca//images/teacher.jpg" title="teacher" ></p>

<p>When there are so many self-help books on the market, how many can you buy, and how do you know which ones will actually be useful?  The answer is easy!  Look for the educational resources that have been developed by experienced educators who have a strong reputation for helping student achieve remarkable results.</p>

<!--more-->


<p>All the <strong><a href="http://www.diplomax.ca">DIPLOMAX.ca</a></strong> and <strong><em>iPrep Plus</em></strong> Electronic Study Notes and Video Support resource packages have been created by actual teachers who understand what you need to know to be successful in the subject.  The educator/authors have provided a comprehensive overview of the Grade 12 course material in language you can understand, included tips for reviewing, and filmed video support clips on the “tough topics” that seem to present challenges to students.</p>

<p>The veteran educators use their knowledge of curriculum, instruction, assessment, expertise, extensive experiences in developing diploma exam questions and marking provincial exams, and their passion for the subject to create strong resources.  Each product focuses on concepts and skills you need to master to maximize your results!</p>

<p>Many of the authors are provincial nominees and Teacher of Excellence Award winners.  Visit the <strong><a href="http://www.diplomax.ca">DIPLOMAX</a> </strong>web site www.diplomax.ca to meet our team of authors and educators.  You may even recognize some of these outstanding educators!</p>

<p><a href="http://www.diplomax.ca">DIPLOMAX.ca</a>
Year-long Support to Classroom Learning.</p>

<p><strong>Not only Authors BUT Exceptional Educators</strong></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Finding Help to Support Classroom Learning]]></title>
    <link href="http://blog.diplomax.ca//finding-help-to-support-classroom-learning/"/>
    <updated>2017-04-22T20:43:29-06:00</updated>
    <id>http://blog.diplomax.ca//finding-help-to-support-classroom-learning</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="center" src="http://blog.diplomax.ca//images/sweat-confusion.jpg" title="confused" ></p>

<p>How many times have you left class and thought <em>“None of this makes sense to me!</em>”?  How many times have you felt your confidence drain away as your tried to complete a major assignment?  How many times have you tried unsuccessfully to apply the formulas you thought you understood in class, to your homework questions to find that you couldn’t remember the steps in the process?  Nothing is more frustrating than trying your hardest to do well but not having the extra help at home when you need it most!</p>

<!--more-->


<p><a href="http://www.diplomax.ca">DIPLOMAX.ca</a> has just what you are looking for!  The <strong>iPrep Plus Electronic Study Notes and Video Support</strong>  resources are unique.  Each resource combines a comprehensive study notes package with short videos on the most challenging course topics to provide you a means of independently reviewing your course content and clarifying your understanding.  You can use the materials to help you with homework assignments, prepare for unit tests and quizzes, completing projects, and reviewing classroom learning.  Watch the videos as many time as needed to ensure you understand the concept.  It’s like having a personal tutor on stand-by while you do your studying at home.</p>

<p>Still not certain if the <strong>iPrep Plus Electronic Study Notes and Video Support</strong> resources will meet your needs?  Then visit www.diplomax.ca  Choose your subject – Biology 30, Chemistry 30, English 30-1, Math 30-1, Math 30-2, Physics 30, Science 30, or Social 30-1.  Watch some of the sample videos and review the sample pages from the resources.  Check out the color-coding in the resources intended to give you hints and help you to remember key strategies and concepts.  Each resource is approximately 50-150 pages that you can download or print.  Each subject has 10 videos of 8-10 minutes in length that focus on the most challenging concepts of the course.</p>

<p>The <strong>iPrep Plus Electronic Study Notes and Video Support</strong> resources provide you with year-long support for approximately the same cost as one hour of traditional tutoring.  When you need the extra help at home, these resources give you the necessary support.  What are you waiting for?  Check it out!</p>

<p><a href="http://www.diplomax.ca">DIPLOMAX.ca</a>
Year-long Support to Classroom Learning.
<strong>Not only Authors BUT Exceptional Educators</strong></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Comes Next?]]></title>
    <link href="http://blog.diplomax.ca//what-comes-next/"/>
    <updated>2017-04-12T18:06:00-06:00</updated>
    <id>http://blog.diplomax.ca//what-comes-next</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="center" src="http://blog.diplomax.ca//images/what_comes_next.jpg" title="what_comes_next" ></p>

<p>Remember when you started school and everyone asked you what you wanted to be when you grew up?  It seemed like there were endless possibilities and lots of time for you to decide what you wanted to be and what you wanted do.  Now, suddenly it seems, you are ending your high school career and people are again asking you, “What are you going to do?”  “What comes next?” is a BIG question – and being a Super Hero is a less likely career option.</p>

<!--more-->


<p>For some, the path is clear – high school to post-secondary to career apprenticeship and employment.  The challenges along this path are getting strong enough grades to be accepted into quota faculties and elite training centres and qualifying for as many scholarships as possible to pay for the necessary accreditation which comes at graduation time.</p>

<p>For others, the path may not be as straight forward and require a more “experiential” approach.  The challenges become based on everyday decisions and immediate circumstances.  Questions such as “Am I qualified to do this job?”, “Do I have the physical and mental stamina to be a success at this?”, “What are the future opportunities for me in this employment setting?”.</p>

<p>Whether or not you know “What comes next?”, one thing is for certain.  You need to keep as many doors to opportunity open as possible.  You need strong grades on your diploma exams so you can confidently apply to the post-secondary institution of your choice or be considered for the apprenticeship position in the newest “disruptor” industry.</p>

<p>During these last few months of the school year, give it all you’ve got!  Check out the many products and services available from <a href="http://www.diplomax.ca">DIPLOMAX.ca</a> to help you get the best grades possible.  You can choose face-to-face sessions, video review sessions, electronic study notes and video support – or any combination!  This is as close to “custom -made studying materials” as is possible.  You can check out the web site <a href="http://www.diplomax.ca">DIPLOMAX.ca</a> for more information. Just remember – “What comes next?” is up to you!</p>

<p><a href="http://www.diplomax.ca">DIPLOMAX.ca</a>
Year-long Support to Classroom Learning.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Second Semester Study Options]]></title>
    <link href="http://blog.diplomax.ca//second-semester-study-options/"/>
    <updated>2017-04-03T19:26:14-06:00</updated>
    <id>http://blog.diplomax.ca//second-semester-study-options</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="center" src="http://blog.diplomax.ca//images/coffee_book.jpg" title="iPrep" ></p>

<p>The new semester is now underway!  We are pleased to remind you that <a href="http://www.diplomax.ca">DIPLOMAX.ca</a> is now accepting registrations for the June <strong>DIPLOMAX In-Class</strong> sessions.  Check out the schedule and register early to secure a spot in the class and session of your choice. Remember – as soon as you complete your registration, you can immediately start to use the Instructor’s Study Notes package to support your classroom instruction.</p>

<!--more-->


<p></p>

<p>If you are not able to attend the DIPLOMAX In-Class sessions, check out the <strong>DIPLOMAX On-Line</strong> sessions and the <strong>iPrep Plus Electronic Study Notes and Video Support</strong> resources.  DIPLOMAX On-Line provides you with a complete video review of the course content – just like the DIPLOMAX In-Class session.  And, you receive a complimentary copy of the Instructor’s Study Notes to download or print.  It’s like being at the session only you can access the video review whenever you want and replay the instruction as many times as you want.  There is no need to download the video review.  You can stream the review on any of your devices.</p>

<p>The <strong>iPrep Plus Electronic Study Notes and Video Support</strong> resources offer you a completely different form of course review than either the DIPLOMAX In-Class or On-Line course review.  The Electronic Study Notes are color-coded to provide you with hints and reminders about various topics and strategies as you work your way through the subject material.  There are 10, short, 8-10 minute videos which focus on the most challenging concepts in each course.  Between the study notes and the videos, you have a very comprehensive review package!</p>

<p>Check out the 3-course semester bundle!  It’s an economical way to help you prepare for your diploma exams whether you are writing them in January, April, June, August or November.</p>

<p><a href="http://www.diplomax.ca">DIPLOMAX.ca</a>
Year-long Support to Classroom Learning.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Strong Finish or a New Start?]]></title>
    <link href="http://blog.diplomax.ca//a-strong-finish-or-a-new-start/"/>
    <updated>2017-01-04T22:57:41-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://blog.diplomax.ca//a-strong-finish-or-a-new-start</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="center" src="http://blog.diplomax.ca//images/happy_new_year.png" title="iPrep" ></p>

<p>Whether you want to finish your first semester with a strong showing or start 2017 with a new self-
assured manner, you can do BOTH by acing your diploma exams!! There is no better feeling than
knowing you are well-prepared and ready to <strong>give it your all</strong> as you write your final test in your course
– the <strong>DIPLOMA EXAM</strong>!! Your grades on each exam combined with your school grades will affect
applications to post-secondary institutions, opportunities to secure scholarships, and employment
opportunities.</p>

<!--more-->


<p></p>

<p>As the first semester of your senior year in high school is coming to an end, be sure you end with a
strong finish! Enroll in a two-day diploma prep class offered by <a href="http://www.diplomax.ca">DIPLOMAX.ca</a>. Check out the many
weekend classes that are offered this January at <a href="http://www.diplomax.ca">DIPLOMAX.ca</a> <em>Be prepared – don’t be sorry</em>!</p>

<p>Check out <a href="http://www.diplomax.ca">DIPLOMAX.ca</a> for the schedule of review sessions, FAQs, facility photos, arriving for the first class, and to register in the class of your choice.  Don’t delay as space is limited!</p>

<p><a href="http://www.diplomax.ca">DIPLOMAX.ca</a>
Year-long Support to Classroom Learning.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[iPrep Plus – Electronic Study Notes and Video Support]]></title>
    <link href="http://blog.diplomax.ca//iprep-plus-electronic-study-notes-and-video-support/"/>
    <updated>2016-12-18T10:14:00-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://blog.diplomax.ca//iprep-plus-electronic-study-notes-and-video-support</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="center" src="http://blog.diplomax.ca//images/iprep.png" title="iPrep" ></p>

<p>The <strong>iPrep Plus Electronic Study Notes and Video Support</strong> resources are unique!  The resources are an electronic resource package that can be downloaded to a personal device or printed and used at home.  They combine comprehensive study notes with short videos to help you independently review course content and clarify understanding.</p>

<!--more-->


<p></p>

<p>The color-coding in the electronic study notes provides hints, reminders, and important things to remember about key concepts.  The electronic study notes can assist you in completing class assignments, reviewing for in-class unit tests and quizzes, and preparing for the diploma exams.  Each resource is from 50-150 pages in length and covers the complete course content.</p>

<p>The resource package also includes <em>10 Support Videos</em> designed to support classroom instruction and learning.  Each video is approximately 8 to 12 minutes in length and focuses on the ‘tough topics’ that students often find challenging.  You can watch the videos as many times as needed to ensure you understand the concept and are confident in your ability to interpret and apply the information in your daily life.</p>

<p>iPrep Plus Electronic Study Notes and Video Support resources are available for Biology 30, Chemistry 30, English 30-1, Math 30-1, Math 30-2, Physics 30, Science 30, and Social Studies 30-1.  These resources provide <em>year-long support</em> for approximately the same cost of one hour of traditional tutoring!  You can access them anytime, anywhere, and on any device.  Use the Electronic Study Notes and Video Support resources to help you achieve strong grades at the end of the semester and on the diploma exams!</p>

<p>Check out <a href="http://www.diplomax.ca">DIPLOMAX.ca</a>for the schedule of review sessions, FAQs, facility photos, arriving for the first class, and to register in the class of your choice.  Don’t delay as space is limited!</p>

<p><a href="http://www.diplomax.ca">DIPLOMAX.ca</a>
Year-long Support to Classroom Learning.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[DIPLOMAX In-Class – the Tradition Continues]]></title>
    <link href="http://blog.diplomax.ca//diplomax-in-class-the-tradition-continues/"/>
    <updated>2016-11-03T22:09:11-06:00</updated>
    <id>http://blog.diplomax.ca//diplomax-in-class-the-tradition-continues</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="center" src="http://blog.diplomax.ca//images/blog-nov-3.png" title="Question" ></p>

<p>Tutorial and diploma prep classes have long been offering services to students preparing to write the January and June provincial diploma exams.  For Edmonton and area students, DIPLOMAX In-Class is offering face-to-face, diploma prep review sessions in Biology 30, Chemistry 30, English 30-1, Math 30-1, Math 30-2, Physics 30, Science 30, and Social 30-1.  The comprehensive review sessions in each subject are scheduled from 9:00 am to 5:00 pm on Saturday and Sunday. The classes are held at the University of Alberta Edmonton Campus.  The two-day format makes it easier for students who work or are travelling from surrounding areas to participate in the review sessions.</p>

<!--more-->


<p></p>

<p>Experienced instructors, with a reputation for getting exceptional results with their students, take you through a comprehensive review of the course curriculum and provide you with tips and strategies for writing the diploma exams.  By working through sample questions, you become familiar with the question formats commonly used to test your understanding and the errors students typically make in their responses.  The bonus is you are able to download or print a personal copy of the Instructor’s Study Notes as soon as you complete your registration!  Having the Study Notes available to you immediately gives you more time for review and addressing any course concepts you find particularly challenging.</p>

<p>Check out <a href="http://www.diplomax.ca">DIPLOMAX.ca</a>for the schedule of review sessions, FAQs, facility photos, arriving for the first class, and to register in the class of your choice.  Don’t delay as space is limited!</p>

<p><a href="http://www.diplomax.ca">DIPLOMAX.ca</a>
Year-long Support to Classroom Learning.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[PRESS RELEASE – PROVINCE-WIDE LAUNCH of DIPLOMAX.CA]]></title>
    <link href="http://blog.diplomax.ca//press-release-province-wide-launch-of-diplomax-dot-ca/"/>
    <updated>2016-10-17T21:21:43-06:00</updated>
    <id>http://blog.diplomax.ca//press-release-province-wide-launch-of-diplomax-dot-ca</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="center" src="http://blog.diplomax.ca//images/DIPLOMAX.CA.png" title="Question" ></p>

<p>Writing any diploma exams this year?  Looking for face-to-face help to prepare for the January or June diplomas?  DIPLOMAX In-Class has it for Edmonton and areas students!  Don’t live close enough to Edmonton to participate?  Don’t worry!  DIPLOMAX On-Line is for you!  It is a comprehensive VIDEO REVIEW that comes with a complimentary copy of the Instructor’s Study Notes.  Looking for something that you can use all year long with class assignments, quizzes and unit tests?  iPrep Plus has just what you are looking for!  Use the electronic study notes with video support for the 10 toughest topics!</p>

<!--more-->


<p></p>

<p><a href="http://www.diplomax.ca">DIPLOMAX.ca</a> is an amazing new service that has the support you need to help you do your best on the diploma exams and your in-class assignments - no matter where you live in Alberta.  As the competition for scholarships and entrance to quota faculties becomes more challenging, it is increasingly important to achieve the highest scores possible on your year-end grades and the provincial diploma exams.  <a href="http://www.diplomax.ca">DIPLOMAX.ca</a> has products and services designed to help you do just that!</p>

<p>Recognizing the need for quality, affordable resources that students can access anytime, anywhere, and on any device, Noel Kunst, noted educator, former assistant superintendent, and now independent consultant, put together a team of experienced and talented instructors to create “what students need” to support their classroom learning and maximize their achievement results.  If you, or anyone you know, is taking Biology 30, Chemistry 30, English 30-1, Math 30-1, Math 30-2, Physics 30, Science 30, or Social 30-1, have them visit www.diplomax.ca to find out more about the new products and services developed especially for them!  Check your school counselling department for printed information about the great products and services available to you through DIPLOMAX.ca!</p>

<p><a href="http://www.diplomax.ca">DIPLOMAX.ca</a>
Year-long Support to Classroom Learning.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[iPrep Plus Gives Students ‘Leg Up’]]></title>
    <link href="http://blog.diplomax.ca//iprep-plus-gives-students-leg-up/"/>
    <updated>2016-05-17T17:42:35-06:00</updated>
    <id>http://blog.diplomax.ca//iprep-plus-gives-students-leg-up</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="center" src="http://blog.diplomax.ca//images/student_edge.jpg" title="Question" ></p>

<p>High-stakes diploma exams in January and June are always a challenge for grade 12 students.   These provincial exams count for 30% of your final grade but the other 70% comes from your efforts on school-based assessments.</p>

<!--more-->


<p></p>

<p>For a variety of reasons, it is becoming more and more common for students to seek assistance beyond the classroom in preparing for the diploma exams.  Entrance requirements for many post-secondary institutions have increased over the years so you need better grades to gain admittance.  The competition is extremely keen for faculties that have quotas and only take the top echelon of applicants.  Then there are the numerous scholarships available for the students who have the top grades!</p>

<p>Teachers work very diligently to get through the extensive, mandated curriculum but often find little time left in the semester for completing a review of the course content.  Students are now looking to external sources for the comprehensive review that will give them the “edge” they need to boost their marks – and open the doors to the future they are seeking.</p>

<p>iPrep Plus gives you exactly what you are looking for! The comprehensive Electronic Study Notes and Video Support resource packages for English 30-1, Biology 30, Chemistry 30, Math 30-1, Math 30-2, Physics 30, Science 30 and Social Studies 30-1 can be used at home to support your classroom learning.  You are provided with a comprehensive course review, video support for the “tough topics”, tips and strategies for writing exams, suggestions for handling exam anxiety, calculator tricks, and effective study hints.</p>

<p>Visit the iPrep Plus web site at www.iPrepPlus.com to watch a “video sampler”, review the course descriptions, and for more information about the introductory price which available for a limited time!</p>

<p>Check out the web site <a href="http://www.iPrepPlus.com">www.iPrepPlus.com</a> for the <strong>introductory price offer</strong> and many features!</p>

<p>If you are serious about your academic success – <strong>iPrep Plus</strong> and <strong>Diplomax</strong> are here to help you!</p>

<p><em>iPrep Plus – Year-long Support for Classroom Learning</em>
More than you imagined for less than you expected – electronic study notes and video support for tough topics!
<a href="http://www.iPrepPlus.com">www.iPrepPlus.com</a></p>

<p><em>Diplomax – Your Premier Choice for Diploma Prep</em>
For Edmonton and area face-to-face review classes in January and June check  <a href="http://www.primetimelearning.ca">www.primetimelearning.ca</a></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Math 30-2 — Sample Question and Solution for Set Theory #3]]></title>
    <link href="http://blog.diplomax.ca//math-30-2-sample-question-and-solution-for-set-theory-number-3/"/>
    <updated>2016-05-15T13:26:04-06:00</updated>
    <id>http://blog.diplomax.ca//math-30-2-sample-question-and-solution-for-set-theory-number-3</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Try this sample question to gauge your diploma preparation for Math 30-2!</p>

<p><img class="center" src="http://blog.diplomax.ca//images/question_SetTheory_1.png" title="Question" ></p>

<!--more-->


<p></p>

<p><img class="center" src="http://blog.diplomax.ca//images/question_SetTheory_2.png" title="Question" ></p>

<p><img class="center" src="http://blog.diplomax.ca//images/question_SetTheory_3.png" title="Question" ></p>

<p>Check out the web site <a href="http://www.iPrepPlus.com">www.iPrepPlus.com</a> for the <strong>introductory price offer</strong> and many features!</p>

<p>If you are serious about your academic success – <strong>iPrep Plus</strong> and <strong>Diplomax</strong> are here to help you!</p>

<p><em>iPrep Plus – Year-long Support for Classroom Learning</em>
More than you imagined for less than you expected – electronic study notes and video support for tough topics!
<a href="http://www.iPrepPlus.com">www.iPrepPlus.com</a></p>

<p><em>Diplomax – Your Premier Choice for Diploma Prep</em>
For Edmonton and area face-to-face review classes in January and June check  <a href="http://www.primetimelearning.ca">www.primetimelearning.ca</a></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Study Schedules – Long-term, Short-term, and PANIC!]]></title>
    <link href="http://blog.diplomax.ca//study-schedules-long-term/"/>
    <updated>2016-05-08T12:17:05-06:00</updated>
    <id>http://blog.diplomax.ca//study-schedules-long-term</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="center" src="http://blog.diplomax.ca//images/grades.jpg" title="&#34;Girls with grades&#34;" alt="&#34;Girls with grades&#34;"></p>

<p>Have you ever read the story of <em>The Hare and the Tortoise?</em>  It is a delightful children’s story of a race between two animal friends who each are confident of their ability to win a race.  The Hare sets off to a speedy start and covers a significant amount of territory before deciding he has enough of a head start on the Tortoise that he can stop for a rest.  He settles under a shady tree and enjoys a nap, confident that he can sprint to the finish line well before the Tortoise can catch up to him.</p>

<!--more-->


<p></p>

<p>The Tortoise leaves the start line slowly plodding along the race path.  Though not a flashy racer, he keeps a steady pace and remains focused on getting to the finish line.  He passes the sleeping Hare and soon sees the finish line looming in the distance.  As the Tortoise is within steps of crossing the finish line and winning the race, the Hare wakes up.  He realizes he needs to make a spirited sprint to overtake the Tortoise.  Unfortunately, the Hare’s panicked dash for the finish line is “too little too late”.  The Tortoise, although a long shot, wins the race and the brazen, confident Hare is left humiliated and searching for an explanation for his loss.</p>

<p>There are many analogies that can be drawn between the race strategies of the story characters and long-term, short-term, and panic study schedules.</p>

<p><strong>Long-term Study Schedules</strong> generally are implemented well in advance of exam time and require you to set aside regular study time on an on-going basis.  Like the Tortoise a slow and steady approach helps to win the race.  The advantage of a long-term study schedule is that once you establish your study routine, it is quite easy to maintain – and shorter, regular periods of study give you the most benefit!</p>

<p><strong>Short-term Study Schedules</strong> are often implemented several days or weeks before an exam and require you to prioritize the time you spend on each topic or concept.  It may be difficult to find a “starting point”.  Do you focus on the things that are most important in the subject or on the concepts that are most challenging to you? Like the Hare, your focus may change before the end of the race.  You may skim over content that you feel you have a firm understanding of in favor of focusing on topics that feel less confident about.  Your focus may not be as consistent or as strong as it needs to be for the duration of your study or exam preparation time. The advantage of a short-term study schedule is that you gain a sense of confidence as you “check off” the topics and concepts you feel confident about.</p>

<p><img class="right" src="http://blog.diplomax.ca//images/panic.jpeg" title="&#34;Panic&#34;" alt="&#34;Panic&#34;"></p>

<p><strong>Panic Study Schedules</strong> usually happen “the night before” the exam – when you realize that you do not have enough time to adequately prepare for your exam.  Although this study schedule requires the least amount of time commitment, it rarely allows you to achieve your potential.  Like the Hare, leaving too much to the end makes it impossible to finish what needs to be done.  However, any effort is better than doing nothing.</p>

<p>To achieve the grades you want requires effort on your part.  A long-term study schedule gives you the best chance for success.  A short-term study schedule may work well in a course where you have a strong understanding of the concepts.  A Panic Study Schedule is better than not studying at all but may not help you to achieve your course goals over the semester or school year.</p>

<p><strong>Does your study strategy resemble the race strategy of the Hare or the Tortoise?</strong></p>

<p>Check out the web site <a href="http://www.iPrepPlus.com">www.iPrepPlus.com</a> for the <strong>introductory price offer</strong> and many features!</p>

<p>If you are serious about your academic success – <strong>iPrep Plus</strong> and <strong>Diplomax</strong> are here to help you!</p>

<p><em>iPrep Plus – Year-long Support for Classroom Learning</em>
More than you imagined for less than you expected – electronic study notes and video support for tough topics!
<a href="http://www.iPrepPlus.com">www.iPrepPlus.com</a></p>

<p><em>Diplomax – Your Premier Choice for Diploma Prep</em>
For Edmonton and area face-to-face review classes in January and June check  <a href="http://www.primetimelearning.ca">www.primetimelearning.ca</a></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Math 30-1 — Sample Question and Solution for Sinusoidal Functions #2]]></title>
    <link href="http://blog.diplomax.ca//math-30-1-sample-question-and-solution-for-sinusoidal-functions-number-2/"/>
    <updated>2016-05-08T11:56:02-06:00</updated>
    <id>http://blog.diplomax.ca//math-30-1-sample-question-and-solution-for-sinusoidal-functions-number-2</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Try this sample question to gauge your diploma preparation for Math 30-1!</p>

<!--more-->


<p></p>

<p><img class="center" src="http://blog.diplomax.ca//images/question2.png" title="Question" ></p>

<p>Check out the web site <a href="http://www.iPrepPlus.com">www.iPrepPlus.com</a> for the <strong>introductory price offer</strong> and many features!</p>

<p>If you are serious about your academic success – <strong>iPrep Plus</strong> and <strong>Diplomax</strong> are here to help you!</p>

<p><em>iPrep Plus – Year-long Support for Classroom Learning</em>
More than you imagined for less than you expected – electronic study notes and video support for tough topics!
<a href="http://www.iPrepPlus.com">www.iPrepPlus.com</a></p>

<p><em>Diplomax – Your Premier Choice for Diploma Prep</em>
For Edmonton and area face-to-face review classes in January and June check  <a href="http://www.primetimelearning.ca">www.primetimelearning.ca</a></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Math 30-1 — Sample Question and Solution for Exponential Functions #1]]></title>
    <link href="http://blog.diplomax.ca//math-30-sample-question-and-solution-number-1/"/>
    <updated>2016-05-03T17:26:03-06:00</updated>
    <id>http://blog.diplomax.ca//math-30-sample-question-and-solution-number-1</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>High-stakes diploma exams in January and June are always a challenge for grade 12 students. These provincial exams count for 30% of a student’s final grade with the other 70% coming from school-based assessments.</p>

<p>For a variety of reasons, it is becoming more and more common for students to seek assistance beyond the classroom in preparing for the diploma exams. Entrance requirements for many post-secondary institutions have increased over the years so students need better grades to gain admittance. The competition is extremely keen for faculties that have quotas and only take the top echelon of applicants. Then there are the numerous scholarships available for the students who have the top grades.</p>

<p>Try this sample question to gauge your diploma preparation for Math 30-1!</p>

<!--more-->


<p></p>

<p><img class="center" src="http://blog.diplomax.ca//images/question1.png" title="Question" ></p>

<p>Check out the web site <a href="http://www.iPrepPlus.com">www.iPrepPlus.com</a> for the <strong>introductory price offer</strong> and many features!</p>

<p>If you are serious about your academic success – <strong>iPrep Plus</strong> and <strong>Diplomax</strong> are here to help you!</p>

<p><em>iPrep Plus – Year-long Support for Classroom Learning</em>
More than you imagined for less than you expected – electronic study notes and video support for tough topics!
<a href="http://www.iPrepPlus.com">www.iPrepPlus.com</a></p>

<p><em>Diplomax – Your Premier Choice for Diploma Prep</em>
For Edmonton and area face-to-face review classes in January and June check  <a href="http://www.primetimelearning.ca">www.primetimelearning.ca</a></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Not Only Authors but Exceptional Educators]]></title>
    <link href="http://blog.diplomax.ca//not-only-authors-but-exceptional-educators/"/>
    <updated>2016-05-02T17:20:34-06:00</updated>
    <id>http://blog.diplomax.ca//not-only-authors-but-exceptional-educators</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="center" src="http://blog.diplomax.ca//images/teacher.jpg" title="Social" ></p>

<p>When there are so many self-help books on the market, how many can you buy, and how do you know which ones will actually be useful?  The answer is easy!  Look for the educational resources that have been developed by experienced educators who have a strong reputation for helping student achieve remarkable results.</p>

<!--more-->


<p></p>

<p>All of the <strong><em>iPrep Plus</em></strong> Electronic Study Notes and Video Support resource packages have been created by actual teachers who understand what students need to know to be successful in the subject.  The <strong><em>iPrep Plus</em></strong> authors have provided a comprehensive overview of the Grade 12 course material in language you can understand, included tips for reviewing, and filmed video support clips on the “tough topics” that seem to present challenges to students.</p>

<p>The veteran educators use their knowledge of curriculum, instruction, assessment, expertise, extensive experiences in developing diploma exam questions and marking provincial exams, and their passion for the subject to create strong resources.  Each Electronic Study Notes and Video Support resource is focused on concepts and skills students need to master to maximize their results!</p>

<p>Many of the authors are provincial nominees and Teacher of Excellence Award winners.  Visit the <strong><em>iPrep Plus</em></strong> web site  <a href="http://www.iPrepPlus.com">www.iPrepPlus.com</a>  and click on Educators’ Bios.  You may even recognize some of these outstanding educators!</p>

<p>Check out the web site <a href="http://www.iPrepPlus.com">www.iPrepPlus.com</a> for the <strong>introductory price offer</strong> and many features!</p>

<p>If you are serious about your academic success – <strong>iPrep Plus</strong> and <strong>Diplomax</strong> are here to help you!</p>

<p><em>iPrep Plus – Year-long Support for Classroom Learning</em>
More than you imagined for less than you expected – electronic study notes and video support for tough topics!
<a href="http://www.iPrepPlus.com">www.iPrepPlus.com</a></p>

<p><em>Diplomax – Your Premier Choice for Diploma Prep</em>
For Edmonton and area face-to-face review classes in January and June check  <a href="http://www.primetimelearning.ca">www.primetimelearning.ca</a></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[iPrep Plus Is Going Social!]]></title>
    <link href="http://blog.diplomax.ca//iprep-plus-is-going-social/"/>
    <updated>2016-04-28T20:40:00-06:00</updated>
    <id>http://blog.diplomax.ca//iprep-plus-is-going-social</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="center" src="http://blog.diplomax.ca//images/Social-media-for-public-relations1.jpg" title="Social" ></p>

<p>Thinking about post-secondary studies?  Trying to qualify for a quota faculty?  Looking at applying for a scholarship?  Worrying about getting your high school diploma? You need to check out the new iPrep Plus Electronic Study Notes and Video Support resource packages
to support your classroom learning!</p>

<!--more-->


<p></p>

<p>Follow iPrep Plus on <a href="https://www.facebook.com/getiPrepPlus/">Facebook</a> and on <a href="https://twitter.com/getiPrepPlus/">Twitter</a>  to get information on:</p>

<ul>
<li>tips and strategies on how to maximize your academic performance</li>
<li>comprehensive Electronic Study Notes and Video Support resource packages for English 30-1, Biology 30, Chemistry 30, Math 30-1, Math 30-2, Physics 30, Science 30, and Social Studies 30-1</li>
<li>techniques for dealing with exam anxiety</li>
<li>practical test writing strategies – including calculator ‘tricks’</li>
<li>strategies for answering multiple choice questions</li>
<li>tips for writing strong thesis statements, essays, and personal responses</li>
<li>comprehension clues to decode meaning</li>
<li>effective study tips</li>
<li>how to prepare for an exam; how to write an exam</li>
</ul>


<p>Check out the web site <a href="http://www.iPrepPlus.com">www.iPrepPlus.com</a> for the <strong>introductory price offer</strong> and many features!</p>

<p>If you are serious about your academic success – <strong>iPrep Plus</strong> and <strong>Diplomax</strong> are here to help you!</p>

<p><em>iPrep Plus – Year-long Support for Classroom Learning</em>
More than you imagined for less than you expected – electronic study notes and video support for tough topics!
<a href="http://www.iPrepPlus.com">www.iPrepPlus.com</a></p>

<p><em>Diplomax – Your Premier Choice for Diploma Prep</em>
For Edmonton and area face-to-face review classes in January and June check  <a href="http://www.primetimelearning.ca">www.primetimelearning.ca</a></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[iPrep Plus (Sequel Solutions Inc.) – SPECIAL OFFER]]></title>
    <link href="http://blog.diplomax.ca//iprep-plus-sequel-solutions-inc-dot-special-offer/"/>
    <updated>2016-04-18T08:20:04-06:00</updated>
    <id>http://blog.diplomax.ca//iprep-plus-sequel-solutions-inc-dot-special-offer</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>PrimeTime Learning and Sequel Solutions Inc. have recently entered into an ‘alliance’ to better serve the educational product/service needs of Grade 12 students in Alberta.</p>

<p><img src="http://blog.diplomax.ca//images/iprem_primetime_2.png" title="iPrepPlus" alt="iPrepPlus" /></p>

<p>To commemorate the alliance, Sequel Solutions Inc. is offering students who purchase four or more iPrep Plus resources a complimentary copy of the 58 page electronic resource ‘Finding Employment’.</p>

<!--more-->


<p></p>

<p>Students who order four or more courses will have ‘Finding Employment’ automatically included in their package of courses.  As with all iPrep Plus resources, ‘Finding Employment’ will need to be saved and/or printed for future use.</p>

<p>In completing the personal analysis found in ‘Finding Employment’ you will have:</p>

<ul>
<li>Identified your personal and professional strengths; become aware of your skills and their alignment with your desired career or job.</li>
<li>Completed a marketplace search for employment opportunities; become familiar with the documentation required in applying for a job and completing a resume.</li>
<li>Reviewed the steps in the interview process; accessed ‘hints’ for making your job interview a ‘success’.</li>
<li>Looked at suggestions for keeping a job; determined what needs to change if you are at first ‘unsuccessful’.</li>
</ul>


<p>Find your ideal summer job, volunteer opportunity – or take steps towards securing a permanent job in your chosen career path!</p>

<p>Check out the web site <a href="http://www.iPrepPlus.com">www.iPrepPlus.com</a> for the <strong>introductory price offer</strong> and many features!</p>

<p>If you are serious about your academic success – <strong>iPrep Plus</strong> and <strong>Diplomax</strong> are here to help you!</p>

<p><em>iPrep Plus – Year-long Support for Classroom Learning</em>
More than you imagined for less than you expected – electronic study notes and video support for tough topics!
<a href="http://www.iPrepPlus.com">www.iPrepPlus.com</a></p>

<p><em>Diplomax – Your Premier Choice for Diploma Prep</em>
For Edmonton and area face-to-face review classes in January and June check  <a href="http://www.primetimelearning.ca">www.primetimelearning.ca</a></p>

<p>Sequel Solutions Inc. (iPrep Plus)
www.iprepplus.com</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Diplomax (PrimeTime Learning) – SPECIAL OFFER]]></title>
    <link href="http://blog.diplomax.ca//diplomax-primetime-learning-special-offer/"/>
    <updated>2016-04-18T08:20:02-06:00</updated>
    <id>http://blog.diplomax.ca//diplomax-primetime-learning-special-offer</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>PrimeTime Learning and Sequel Solutions Inc. have recently entered into an ‘alliance’ to better serve the educational product/service needs of Grade 12 students in Alberta.</p>

<p><img src="http://blog.diplomax.ca//images/iprem_primetime_1.png" title="Diplomax" alt="Diplomax" /></p>

<p>To commemorate the alliance, PrimeTime Learning is offering students who register for three or more Diplomax courses in a semester, an entry into a year-end ‘scholarship draw’.</p>

<!--more-->


<p></p>

<p>Eligible students will be informed by e-mail of their entry into the draw for one of four $250 scholarships.  The draws will take place on June 30th, winners will be contacted, and results reported on the PrimeTime Learning website.</p>

<p>Winning students will have $250 to use in whatever manner they choose.</p>

<ul>
<li>Some will choose to apply the funds to the many costs associated with tuition, or books and materials for their post-secondary education.</li>
<li>Others may choose to apply the funds to costs associated with entering their first career or job.</li>
<li>Still others may decide to ‘reward’ themselves with a summer vacation or trip.</li>
<li>The funds are provided to the winners of the draw with ‘no strings attached’ – please use them in the way you believe is best for you.</li>
</ul>


<p>Check out the web site <a href="http://www.iPrepPlus.com">www.iPrepPlus.com</a> for the <strong>introductory price offer</strong> and many features!</p>

<p>If you are serious about your academic success – <strong>iPrep Plus</strong> and <strong>Diplomax</strong> are here to help you!</p>

<p><em>iPrep Plus – Year-long Support for Classroom Learning</em>
More than you imagined for less than you expected – electronic study notes and video support for tough topics!
<a href="http://www.iPrepPlus.com">www.iPrepPlus.com</a></p>

<p><em>Diplomax – Your Premier Choice for Diploma Prep</em>
For Edmonton and area face-to-face review classes in January and June check  <a href="http://www.primetimelearning.ca">www.primetimelearning.ca</a></p>

<p>Best of luck!
PrimeTime Learning (Diplomax)</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[PRESS RELEASE]]></title>
    <link href="http://blog.diplomax.ca//press-release/"/>
    <updated>2016-04-05T22:14:38-06:00</updated>
    <id>http://blog.diplomax.ca//press-release</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Two of the province&rsquo;s most respected educational companies have recently joined forces - an ALLIANCE designed to provide GRADE 12 STUDENTS with an even STRONGER RANGE of PRODUCTS and SERVICES!</p>

<p><img src="http://blog.diplomax.ca//images/iprem_primetime.png" title="Noel Kunst" alt="Noel Kunst" /></p>

<!--more-->


<p></p>

<p>The unique, complementary services provided by Primetime Learning and iPrep Plus enables Alberta students to access Face-to-Face Diploma Exam Prep, as well as Year-long Study Support at Home.</p>

<p>PrimeTime Learning offers, through Diplomax - 16 hours of review for Diploma exam subjects, in January and June of each year, at the University of Alberta, in Edmonton.</p>

<p>iPrep Plus provides, through electronic Study Notes and Video Support for the &lsquo;tough topics&rsquo;, year-long support to assist in completing homework, preparing for term tests, and reviewing for diploma exams.</p>

<p>To celebrate their expansion of services, each company is offering students a SPECIAL OFFER when ordering multiple courses.  Check out the details on the respective websites.</p>

<p>Check out the web site <a href="http://www.iPrepPlus.com">www.iPrepPlus.com</a> for the <strong>introductory price offer</strong> and many features!</p>

<p>If you are serious about your academic success – <strong>iPrep Plus</strong> and <strong>Diplomax</strong> are here to help you!</p>

<p><em>iPrep Plus – Year-long Support for Classroom Learning</em>
More than you imagined for less than you expected – electronic study notes and video support for tough topics!
<a href="http://www.iPrepPlus.com">www.iPrepPlus.com</a></p>

<p><em>Diplomax – Your Premier Choice for Diploma Prep</em>
For Edmonton and area face-to-face review classes in January and June check  <a href="http://www.primetimelearning.ca">www.primetimelearning.ca</a></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tell Us What You Think]]></title>
    <link href="http://blog.diplomax.ca//tell-us-what-you-think/"/>
    <updated>2016-03-20T10:16:07-06:00</updated>
    <id>http://blog.diplomax.ca//tell-us-what-you-think</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="center" src="http://blog.diplomax.ca//images/CULTURE1.jpg" title="Students" ></p>

<p>Now that you are responsible for 70% of your final grade, your efforts have a more significant impact on your final results.  <strong>iPrep Plus</strong> is a new offering that provides you with resources you can use at home to support your classroom learning.   We think the combination of electronic study notes and video support provides you with the best opportunity to optimize your learning.  However, we need to hear from you!</p>

<!--more-->


<p></p>

<p>We are interested in knowing what aspects of the resource package worked well for you.  Your feedback will help us to continue to improve our product.  Your testimonial will help to “spread the word” about a unique product designed to help you complete classroom assignments, prepare for unit tests, clarify your understanding, and study for the diploma exams.</p>

<p>Share your comments with us at TESTIMONIALS
<a href="http://iprepplus.com/testimonials">http://iprepplus.com/testimonials</a> or visit the <strong>iPrep Plus</strong> web site www.iPrepPlus.com for more information.  If you are serious about your academic success – <strong>iPrep Plus </strong>is here to help you succeed!</p>

<p>Check out the web site <a href="http://www.iPrepPlus.com">www.iPrepPlus.com</a> for the <strong>introductory price offer</strong> and many features!</p>

<p>If you are serious about your academic success – <strong>iPrep Plus</strong> and <strong>Diplomax</strong> are here to help you!</p>

<p><em>iPrep Plus – Year-long Support for Classroom Learning</em>
More than you imagined for less than you expected – electronic study notes and video support for tough topics!
<a href="http://www.iPrepPlus.com">www.iPrepPlus.com</a></p>

<p><em>Diplomax – Your Premier Choice for Diploma Prep</em>
For Edmonton and area face-to-face review classes in January and June check  <a href="http://www.primetimelearning.ca">www.primetimelearning.ca</a></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
