<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[iPrepPlus]]></title>
  <link href="http://blog.iprepplus.com//atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://blog.iprepplus.com//"/>
  <updated>2015-10-20T21:55:30-06:00</updated>
  <id>http://blog.iprepplus.com//</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[iPrepPlus]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[PRESS RELEASE <br/>DIPLOMAX Co-founder Launches New Service – iPREP PLUS]]></title>
    <link href="http://blog.iprepplus.com//press-release/"/>
    <updated>2015-10-20T19:21:38-06:00</updated>
    <id>http://blog.iprepplus.com//press-release</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>DIPLOMAX co-founder Noel Kunst is pleased to announce the launch of <strong>iPrep Plus – Home Support to Classroom Learning</strong>.  It is a province-wide, complementary service to the popular face-to-face review sessions of DIPLOMAX which are held twice a year in Edmonton to assist students in preparing for the provincial diploma exams.</p>

<p><img src="http://blog.iprepplus.com//images/Noel_Kunst_4935_colour.jpg" title="Noel Kunst" alt="Noel Kunst" /></p>

<p>iPrep Plus provides students with <strong>unlimited access</strong> to an <strong>electronic Study Notes</strong> package and <strong>Video Support</strong> for the “tough topics” in English 30-1, social Studies 30-1, Biology 30, Chemistry 30, Math 30-1, Math 30-2, Physics 30, and Science 30.  The resources can be used anytime, on any device, anywhere to support students in their day-to-day studies, class assignments, quizzes and unit or final tests.  Now that 70% of final grades are assigned by the school, it is more important than ever that students have access to quality materials to support their home study.</p>

<p>The <strong>electronic Study Notes</strong> of 50-150 pages provides a focused and comprehensive review of all course content.  The <strong>Video Support</strong>, comprised of five to ten minutes videos, deals with the “tough topics” of the course identifying common problems or errors students make, and providing a summary of helpful suggestions and hints to overcome and master the challenges.  The best news about <em>iPrep Plus</em> is that students can have <strong>immediate and unlimited access</strong> to all this for <strong>the same cost as one hour of traditional tutoring</strong>!!</p>

<p>Check out the web site <a href="http://www.iPrepPlus.com">www.iPrepPlus.com</a> for the <strong>introductory price offer</strong> and many features!</p>

<p><strong>iPrep Plus – Home Support for Classroom Learning
More than you imagined for less than you expected!</strong></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
