<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Unbelievable Price | iPrepPlus]]></title>
  <link href="http://blog.iprepplus.com//blog/categories/unbelievable-price/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://blog.iprepplus.com//"/>
  <updated>2016-05-02T17:45:24-06:00</updated>
  <id>http://blog.iprepplus.com//</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[iPrepPlus]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Not Only Authors but Exceptional Educators]]></title>
    <link href="http://blog.iprepplus.com//not-only-authors-but-exceptional-educators/"/>
    <updated>2016-05-02T17:20:34-06:00</updated>
    <id>http://blog.iprepplus.com//not-only-authors-but-exceptional-educators</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="center" src="/images/teacher.jpg" title="Social" ></p>

<p>When there are so many self-help books on the market, how many can you buy, and how do you know which ones will actually be useful?  The answer is easy!  Look for the educational resources that have been developed by experienced educators who have a strong reputation for helping student achieve remarkable results.</p>

<!--more-->


<p></p>

<p>All of the <strong><em>iPrep Plus</em></strong> Electronic Study Notes and Video Support resource packages have been created by actual teachers who understand what students need to know to be successful in the subject.  The <strong><em>iPrep Plus</em></strong> authors have provided a comprehensive overview of the Grade 12 course material in language you can understand, included tips for reviewing, and filmed video support clips on the “tough topics” that seem to present challenges to students.</p>

<p>The veteran educators use their knowledge of curriculum, instruction, assessment, expertise, extensive experiences in developing diploma exam questions and marking provincial exams, and their passion for the subject to create strong resources.  Each Electronic Study Notes and Video Support resource is focused on concepts and skills students need to master to maximize their results!</p>

<p>Many of the authors are provincial nominees and Teacher of Excellence Award winners.  Visit the <strong><em>iPrep Plus</em></strong> web site  <a href="http://www.iPrepPlus.com">www.iPrepPlus.com</a>  and click on Educators’ Bios.  You may even recognize some of these outstanding educators!</p>

<p>Check out the web site <a href="http://www.iPrepPlus.com">www.iPrepPlus.com</a> for the <strong>introductory price offer</strong> and many features!</p>

<p>If you are serious about your academic success – <strong>iPrep Plus</strong> and <strong>Diplomax</strong> are here to help you!</p>

<p><em>iPrep Plus – Year-long Support for Classroom Learning</em>
More than you imagined for less than you expected – electronic study notes and video support for tough topics!
<a href="http://www.iPrepPlus.com">www.iPrepPlus.com</a></p>

<p><em>Diplomax – Your Premier Choice for Diploma Prep</em>
For Edmonton and area face-to-face review classes in January and June check  <a href="www.primetimelearning.ca">www.primetimelearning.ca</a></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[iPrep Plus Is Going Social!]]></title>
    <link href="http://blog.iprepplus.com//iprep-plus-is-going-social/"/>
    <updated>2016-04-28T20:40:00-06:00</updated>
    <id>http://blog.iprepplus.com//iprep-plus-is-going-social</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="center" src="/images/Social-media-for-public-relations1.jpg" title="Social" ></p>

<p>Thinking about post-secondary studies?  Trying to qualify for a quota faculty?  Looking at applying for a scholarship?  Worrying about getting your high school diploma? You need to check out the new iPrep Plus Electronic Study Notes and Video Support resource packages
to support your classroom learning!</p>

<!--more-->


<p></p>

<p>Follow iPrep Plus on <a href="https://www.facebook.com/getiPrepPlus/">Facebook</a> and on <a href="https://twitter.com/getiPrepPlus/">Twitter</a>  to get information on:</p>

<ul>
<li>tips and strategies on how to maximize your academic performance</li>
<li>comprehensive Electronic Study Notes and Video Support resource packages for English 30-1, Biology 30, Chemistry 30, Math 30-1, Math 30-2, Physics 30, Science 30, and Social Studies 30-1</li>
<li>techniques for dealing with exam anxiety</li>
<li>practical test writing strategies – including calculator ‘tricks’</li>
<li>strategies for answering multiple choice questions</li>
<li>tips for writing strong thesis statements, essays, and personal responses</li>
<li>comprehension clues to decode meaning</li>
<li>effective study tips</li>
<li>how to prepare for an exam; how to write an exam</li>
</ul>


<p>Check out the web site <a href="http://www.iPrepPlus.com">www.iPrepPlus.com</a> for the <strong>introductory price offer</strong> and many features!</p>

<p>If you are serious about your academic success – <strong>iPrep Plus</strong> and <strong>Diplomax</strong> are here to help you!</p>

<p><em>iPrep Plus – Year-long Support for Classroom Learning</em>
More than you imagined for less than you expected – electronic study notes and video support for tough topics!
<a href="http://www.iPrepPlus.com">www.iPrepPlus.com</a></p>

<p><em>Diplomax – Your Premier Choice for Diploma Prep</em>
For Edmonton and area face-to-face review classes in January and June check  <a href="www.primetimelearning.ca">www.primetimelearning.ca</a></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exceptional Value – Unbelievable Price – Limited Time Offer]]></title>
    <link href="http://blog.iprepplus.com//exceptional-value-unbelievable-price-limited-time-offer/"/>
    <updated>2016-01-13T21:58:56-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://blog.iprepplus.com//exceptional-value-unbelievable-price-limited-time-offer</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="center" src="/images/blog_4.jpg" title="Students" ></p>

<p>For only $60 – about the same price as one hour of face-to-face tutoring – you can get year-long access to electronic study notes and video support for most 30-level subjects!</p>

<!--more-->


<p></p>

<p>How many times have you wanted “just a little extra help” with a tough topic or another way to review your classroom materials?  Now you can!  Each iPrep Plus Electronic Study Notes and Video Support resource package gives you a comprehensive review of your course material and five video support clips to help you improve your understanding of the “tough topics”.  Each video support clip is approximately five to 10 minutes in length – and you can watch it as many times as you want.  Use the resources to help you prepare for class quizzes, assignments, unit tests, and semester exams.</p>

<p>Visit the iPrep Plus web site www.iPrepPlus.com  to check out all of the features for English 30-1, Biology 30, Chemistry 30, Math 30-1, Math 30-2, Physics 30, Science 30, and Social Studies 30-1.  Browse the course content overview.  Watch the “Video Samplers” for each subject.  This is a great offer but it won’t last forever!  Order your resources now!</p>

<p>Check out the web site <a href="http://www.iPrepPlus.com">www.iPrepPlus.com</a> for the <strong>introductory price offer</strong> and many features!</p>

<p>If you are serious about your academic success – <strong>iPrep Plus</strong> and <strong>Diplomax</strong> are here to help you!</p>

<p><em>iPrep Plus – Year-long Support for Classroom Learning</em>
More than you imagined for less than you expected – electronic study notes and video support for tough topics!
<a href="http://www.iPrepPlus.com">www.iPrepPlus.com</a></p>

<p><em>Diplomax – Your Premier Choice for Diploma Prep</em>
For Edmonton and area face-to-face review classes in January and June check  <a href="www.primetimelearning.ca">www.primetimelearning.ca</a></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
