<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Introduction | Diplomax]]></title>
  <link href="http://blog.diplomax.ca//blog/categories/introduction/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://blog.diplomax.ca//"/>
  <updated>2018-05-12T11:38:54-06:00</updated>
  <id>http://blog.diplomax.ca//</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Diplomax]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[iPrep Plus (Sequel Solutions Inc.) – SPECIAL OFFER]]></title>
    <link href="http://blog.diplomax.ca//iprep-plus-sequel-solutions-inc-dot-special-offer/"/>
    <updated>2016-04-18T08:20:04-06:00</updated>
    <id>http://blog.diplomax.ca//iprep-plus-sequel-solutions-inc-dot-special-offer</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>PrimeTime Learning and Sequel Solutions Inc. have recently entered into an ‘alliance’ to better serve the educational product/service needs of Grade 12 students in Alberta.</p>

<p><img src="/images/iprem_primetime_2.png" title="iPrepPlus" alt="iPrepPlus" /></p>

<p>To commemorate the alliance, Sequel Solutions Inc. is offering students who purchase four or more iPrep Plus resources a complimentary copy of the 58 page electronic resource ‘Finding Employment’.</p>

<!--more-->


<p></p>

<p>Students who order four or more courses will have ‘Finding Employment’ automatically included in their package of courses.  As with all iPrep Plus resources, ‘Finding Employment’ will need to be saved and/or printed for future use.</p>

<p>In completing the personal analysis found in ‘Finding Employment’ you will have:</p>

<ul>
<li>Identified your personal and professional strengths; become aware of your skills and their alignment with your desired career or job.</li>
<li>Completed a marketplace search for employment opportunities; become familiar with the documentation required in applying for a job and completing a resume.</li>
<li>Reviewed the steps in the interview process; accessed ‘hints’ for making your job interview a ‘success’.</li>
<li>Looked at suggestions for keeping a job; determined what needs to change if you are at first ‘unsuccessful’.</li>
</ul>


<p>Find your ideal summer job, volunteer opportunity – or take steps towards securing a permanent job in your chosen career path!</p>

<p>Check out the web site <a href="http://www.iPrepPlus.com">www.iPrepPlus.com</a> for the <strong>introductory price offer</strong> and many features!</p>

<p>If you are serious about your academic success – <strong>iPrep Plus</strong> and <strong>Diplomax</strong> are here to help you!</p>

<p><em>iPrep Plus – Year-long Support for Classroom Learning</em>
More than you imagined for less than you expected – electronic study notes and video support for tough topics!
<a href="http://www.iPrepPlus.com">www.iPrepPlus.com</a></p>

<p><em>Diplomax – Your Premier Choice for Diploma Prep</em>
For Edmonton and area face-to-face review classes in January and June check  <a href="http://www.primetimelearning.ca">www.primetimelearning.ca</a></p>

<p>Sequel Solutions Inc. (iPrep Plus)
www.iprepplus.com</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Diplomax (PrimeTime Learning) – SPECIAL OFFER]]></title>
    <link href="http://blog.diplomax.ca//diplomax-primetime-learning-special-offer/"/>
    <updated>2016-04-18T08:20:02-06:00</updated>
    <id>http://blog.diplomax.ca//diplomax-primetime-learning-special-offer</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>PrimeTime Learning and Sequel Solutions Inc. have recently entered into an ‘alliance’ to better serve the educational product/service needs of Grade 12 students in Alberta.</p>

<p><img src="/images/iprem_primetime_1.png" title="Diplomax" alt="Diplomax" /></p>

<p>To commemorate the alliance, PrimeTime Learning is offering students who register for three or more Diplomax courses in a semester, an entry into a year-end ‘scholarship draw’.</p>

<!--more-->


<p></p>

<p>Eligible students will be informed by e-mail of their entry into the draw for one of four $250 scholarships.  The draws will take place on June 30th, winners will be contacted, and results reported on the PrimeTime Learning website.</p>

<p>Winning students will have $250 to use in whatever manner they choose.</p>

<ul>
<li>Some will choose to apply the funds to the many costs associated with tuition, or books and materials for their post-secondary education.</li>
<li>Others may choose to apply the funds to costs associated with entering their first career or job.</li>
<li>Still others may decide to ‘reward’ themselves with a summer vacation or trip.</li>
<li>The funds are provided to the winners of the draw with ‘no strings attached’ – please use them in the way you believe is best for you.</li>
</ul>


<p>Check out the web site <a href="http://www.iPrepPlus.com">www.iPrepPlus.com</a> for the <strong>introductory price offer</strong> and many features!</p>

<p>If you are serious about your academic success – <strong>iPrep Plus</strong> and <strong>Diplomax</strong> are here to help you!</p>

<p><em>iPrep Plus – Year-long Support for Classroom Learning</em>
More than you imagined for less than you expected – electronic study notes and video support for tough topics!
<a href="http://www.iPrepPlus.com">www.iPrepPlus.com</a></p>

<p><em>Diplomax – Your Premier Choice for Diploma Prep</em>
For Edmonton and area face-to-face review classes in January and June check  <a href="http://www.primetimelearning.ca">www.primetimelearning.ca</a></p>

<p>Best of luck!
PrimeTime Learning (Diplomax)</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[PRESS RELEASE]]></title>
    <link href="http://blog.diplomax.ca//press-release/"/>
    <updated>2016-04-05T22:14:38-06:00</updated>
    <id>http://blog.diplomax.ca//press-release</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Two of the province&rsquo;s most respected educational companies have recently joined forces - an ALLIANCE designed to provide GRADE 12 STUDENTS with an even STRONGER RANGE of PRODUCTS and SERVICES!</p>

<p><img src="/images/iprem_primetime.png" title="Noel Kunst" alt="Noel Kunst" /></p>

<!--more-->


<p></p>

<p>The unique, complementary services provided by Primetime Learning and iPrep Plus enables Alberta students to access Face-to-Face Diploma Exam Prep, as well as Year-long Study Support at Home.</p>

<p>PrimeTime Learning offers, through Diplomax - 16 hours of review for Diploma exam subjects, in January and June of each year, at the University of Alberta, in Edmonton.</p>

<p>iPrep Plus provides, through electronic Study Notes and Video Support for the &lsquo;tough topics&rsquo;, year-long support to assist in completing homework, preparing for term tests, and reviewing for diploma exams.</p>

<p>To celebrate their expansion of services, each company is offering students a SPECIAL OFFER when ordering multiple courses.  Check out the details on the respective websites.</p>

<p>Check out the web site <a href="http://www.iPrepPlus.com">www.iPrepPlus.com</a> for the <strong>introductory price offer</strong> and many features!</p>

<p>If you are serious about your academic success – <strong>iPrep Plus</strong> and <strong>Diplomax</strong> are here to help you!</p>

<p><em>iPrep Plus – Year-long Support for Classroom Learning</em>
More than you imagined for less than you expected – electronic study notes and video support for tough topics!
<a href="http://www.iPrepPlus.com">www.iPrepPlus.com</a></p>

<p><em>Diplomax – Your Premier Choice for Diploma Prep</em>
For Edmonton and area face-to-face review classes in January and June check  <a href="http://www.primetimelearning.ca">www.primetimelearning.ca</a></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is iPrepPlus?]]></title>
    <link href="http://blog.diplomax.ca//what-is-iprepplus/"/>
    <updated>2015-12-20T18:00:00-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://blog.diplomax.ca//what-is-iprepplus</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><strong>iPrep Plus</strong> is a unique home support to classroom learning for English 30-1, Biology 30, Chemistry 30, Math 30-1, Math 30-2, Physics 30, Science 30, and Social 30 -1.  Each resource package consists of electronic review notes of 50-150 pages and support videos, each 5-10 minutes in length.  <strong>iPrep Plus</strong> electronic resource packages can be accessed anytime, anywhere and on any device!</p>

<p><img src="/images/shutterstock_64648132.jpg" title="Noel Kunst" alt="Student Studying" /></p>

<!--more-->


<p></p>

<p>All of the electronic resource packages have been developed by well-respected teachers with a reputation for excellence in teaching and achieving exceptional results with students in the classroom and on diploma examinations.</p>

<p><strong>iPrep Plus</strong> provides you with a complete, structured, and comprehensive review of course material and short video clips to help you understand some of the most challenging concepts of a course.  For approximately the same cost as one hour of face-to-face tutoring, you can have <em>unlimited</em> access to the resources for one <strong>iPrep Plus</strong> subject.  You and your school are responsible for 70% of your final grade – maximize your potential!  Use the materials at home to support your course review, class assignments, and exam preparation.</p>

<p>Check out the web site <a href="http://www.iPrepPlus.com">www.iPrepPlus.com</a> for the <strong>introductory price offer</strong> and many features!</p>

<p>If you are serious about your academic success – <strong>iPrep Plus</strong> and <strong>Diplomax</strong> are here to help you!</p>

<p><em>iPrep Plus – Year-long Support for Classroom Learning</em>
More than you imagined for less than you expected – electronic study notes and video support for tough topics!
<a href="http://www.iPrepPlus.com">www.iPrepPlus.com</a></p>

<p><em>Diplomax – Your Premier Choice for Diploma Prep</em>
For Edmonton and area face-to-face review classes in January and June check  <a href="http://www.primetimelearning.ca">www.primetimelearning.ca</a></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[PRESS RELEASE <br/>DIPLOMAX Co-founder Launches New Service – iPREP PLUS]]></title>
    <link href="http://blog.diplomax.ca//press-release/"/>
    <updated>2015-10-20T19:21:38-06:00</updated>
    <id>http://blog.diplomax.ca//press-release</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>DIPLOMAX co-founder Noel Kunst is pleased to announce the launch of <strong>iPrep Plus – Home Support to Classroom Learning</strong>.  It is a province-wide, complementary service to the popular face-to-face review sessions of DIPLOMAX which are held twice a year in Edmonton to assist students in preparing for the provincial diploma exams.</p>

<p><img src="/images/Noel_Kunst_4935_colour.jpg" title="Noel Kunst" alt="Noel Kunst" /></p>

<!--more-->


<p></p>

<p>iPrep Plus provides students with <strong>unlimited access</strong> to an <strong>electronic Study Notes</strong> package and <strong>Video Support</strong> for the “tough topics” in English 30-1, Social Studies 30-1, Biology 30, Chemistry 30, Math 30-1, Math 30-2, Physics 30, and Science 30.  The resources can be used anytime, on any device, anywhere to support students in their day-to-day studies, class assignments, quizzes and unit or final tests.  Now that 70% of final grades are assigned by the school, it is more important than ever that students have access to quality materials to support their home study.</p>

<p>The <strong>electronic Study Notes</strong> of 50-150 pages provides a focused and comprehensive review of all course content.  The <strong>Video Support</strong>, comprised of five to ten minutes videos, deals with the “tough topics” of the course identifying common problems or errors students make, and providing a summary of helpful suggestions and hints to overcome and master the challenges.  The best news about <em>iPrep Plus</em> is that students can have <strong>immediate and unlimited access</strong> to all this for <strong>the same cost as one hour of traditional tutoring</strong>!!</p>

<p>Check out the web site <a href="http://www.iPrepPlus.com">www.iPrepPlus.com</a> for the <strong>introductory price offer</strong> and many features!</p>

<p>If you are serious about your academic success – <strong>iPrep Plus</strong> and <strong>Diplomax</strong> are here to help you!</p>

<p><em>iPrep Plus – Year-long Support for Classroom Learning</em>
More than you imagined for less than you expected – electronic study notes and video support for tough topics!
<a href="http://www.iPrepPlus.com">www.iPrepPlus.com</a></p>

<p><em>Diplomax – Your Premier Choice for Diploma Prep</em>
For Edmonton and area face-to-face review classes in January and June check  <a href="http://www.primetimelearning.ca">www.primetimelearning.ca</a></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
