<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Introduction | iPrepPlus]]></title>
  <link href="http://blog.iprepplus.com//blog/categories/introduction/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://blog.iprepplus.com//"/>
  <updated>2016-03-14T18:24:59-06:00</updated>
  <id>http://blog.iprepplus.com//</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[iPrepPlus]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is iPrepPlus?]]></title>
    <link href="http://blog.iprepplus.com//what-is-iprepplus/"/>
    <updated>2015-12-20T18:00:00-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://blog.iprepplus.com//what-is-iprepplus</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><strong>iPrep Plus</strong> is a unique home support to classroom learning for English 30-1, Biology 30, Chemistry 30, Math 30-1, Math 30-2, Physics 30, Science 30, and Social 30 -1.  Each resource package consists of electronic review notes of 50-150 pages and support videos, each 5-10 minutes in length.  <strong>iPrep Plus</strong> electronic resource packages can be accessed anytime, anywhere and on any device!</p>

<p><img src="/images/shutterstock_64648132.jpg" title="Noel Kunst" alt="Student Studying" /></p>

<!--more-->


<p></p>

<p>All of the electronic resource packages have been developed by well-respected teachers with a reputation for excellence in teaching and achieving exceptional results with students in the classroom and on diploma examinations.</p>

<p><strong>iPrep Plus</strong> provides you with a complete, structured, and comprehensive review of course material and short video clips to help you understand some of the most challenging concepts of a course.  For approximately the same cost as one hour of face-to-face tutoring, you can have <em>unlimited</em> access to the resources for one <strong>iPrep Plus</strong> subject.  You and your school are responsible for 70% of your final grade – maximize your potential!  Use the materials at home to support your course review, class assignments, and exam preparation.</p>

<p>Visit the <strong>iPrep Plus</strong> web site <a href="http://www.iPrepPlus.com">www.iPrepPlus.com</a> for information and introductory pricing. If you are serious about your academic success – iPrep Plus is here to help you succeed!</p>

<p><strong>iPrep Plus – Home Support for Classroom Learning</strong>
<em>More than you imagined for less than you expected!</em></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[PRESS RELEASE <br/>DIPLOMAX Co-founder Launches New Service – iPREP PLUS]]></title>
    <link href="http://blog.iprepplus.com//press-release/"/>
    <updated>2015-10-20T19:21:38-06:00</updated>
    <id>http://blog.iprepplus.com//press-release</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>DIPLOMAX co-founder Noel Kunst is pleased to announce the launch of <strong>iPrep Plus – Home Support to Classroom Learning</strong>.  It is a province-wide, complementary service to the popular face-to-face review sessions of DIPLOMAX which are held twice a year in Edmonton to assist students in preparing for the provincial diploma exams.</p>

<p><img src="/images/Noel_Kunst_4935_colour.jpg" title="Noel Kunst" alt="Noel Kunst" /></p>

<!--more-->


<p></p>

<p>iPrep Plus provides students with <strong>unlimited access</strong> to an <strong>electronic Study Notes</strong> package and <strong>Video Support</strong> for the “tough topics” in English 30-1, Social Studies 30-1, Biology 30, Chemistry 30, Math 30-1, Math 30-2, Physics 30, and Science 30.  The resources can be used anytime, on any device, anywhere to support students in their day-to-day studies, class assignments, quizzes and unit or final tests.  Now that 70% of final grades are assigned by the school, it is more important than ever that students have access to quality materials to support their home study.</p>

<p>The <strong>electronic Study Notes</strong> of 50-150 pages provides a focused and comprehensive review of all course content.  The <strong>Video Support</strong>, comprised of five to ten minutes videos, deals with the “tough topics” of the course identifying common problems or errors students make, and providing a summary of helpful suggestions and hints to overcome and master the challenges.  The best news about <em>iPrep Plus</em> is that students can have <strong>immediate and unlimited access</strong> to all this for <strong>the same cost as one hour of traditional tutoring</strong>!!</p>

<p>Check out the web site <a href="http://www.iPrepPlus.com">www.iPrepPlus.com</a> for the <strong>introductory price offer</strong> and many features!</p>

<p><strong>iPrep Plus – Home Support for Classroom Learning
More than you imagined for less than you expected!</strong></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
