<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: English 30-1 | Diplomax]]></title>
  <link href="http://blog.diplomax.ca//blog/categories/english-30-1/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://blog.diplomax.ca//"/>
  <updated>2017-04-22T20:58:48-06:00</updated>
  <id>http://blog.diplomax.ca//</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Diplomax]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Finding Help to Support Classroom Learning]]></title>
    <link href="http://blog.diplomax.ca//finding-help-to-support-classroom-learning/"/>
    <updated>2017-04-22T20:43:29-06:00</updated>
    <id>http://blog.diplomax.ca//finding-help-to-support-classroom-learning</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="center" src="/images/sweat-confusion.jpg" title="confused" ></p>

<p>How many times have you left class and thought <em>“None of this makes sense to me!</em>”?  How many times have felt your confidence drain away as your tried to complete a major assignment?  How many times have you tried unsuccessfully to apply the formulas you thought you understood in class, to your homework questions to find that you couldn’t remember the steps in the process?  Nothing is more frustrating than trying your hardest to do well but not having the extra help at home when you need it most!</p>

<!--more-->


<p><a href="http://www.diplomax.ca">DIPLOMAX.ca</a>has just what you are looking for!  The <strong>iPrep Plus Electronic Study Notes and Video</strong> Support resources are unique.  Each resource combines a comprehensive study notes package with short videos on the most challenging course topics to provide you a means of independently reviewing your course content and clarifying your understanding.  You can use the materials to help you with homework assignments, prepare for unit tests and quizzes, completing projects, and reviewing classroom learning.  Watch the videos as many time as needed to ensure you understand the concept.  It’s like having a personal tutor on stand-by while you do your studying at home.</p>

<p>Still not certain if the <strong>iPrep Plus Electronic Study Notes and Video Support</strong> resources will meet your needs?  Then visit www.diplomax.ca  Choose your subject – Biology 30, Chemistry 30, English 30-1, Math 30-1, Math 30-2, Physics 30, Science 30, or Social 30-1.  Watch some of the sample videos and review the sample pages from the resources.  Check out the color-coding in the resources intended to give you hints and help you to remember key strategies and concepts.  Each resource is approximately 50-150 pages that you can download or print.  Each subject has 10 videos of 8-10 minutes in length that focus on the most challenging concepts of the course.</p>

<p>The <strong>iPrep Plus Electronic Study Notes and Video Support</strong> resources provide you with year-long support for approximately the same cost as one hour of traditional tutoring.  When you need the extra help at home, these resources give you the necessary support.  What are you waiting for?  Check it out!</p>

<p><a href="http://www.diplomax.ca">DIPLOMAX.ca</a>
Year-long Support to Classroom Learning.
<strong>Not only Authors BUT Exceptional Educators</strong></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Comes Next?]]></title>
    <link href="http://blog.diplomax.ca//what-comes-next/"/>
    <updated>2017-04-12T18:06:00-06:00</updated>
    <id>http://blog.diplomax.ca//what-comes-next</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="center" src="/images/what_comes_next.jpg" title="what_comes_next" ></p>

<p>Remember when you started school and everyone asked you what you wanted to be when you grew up?  It seemed like there were endless possibilities and lots of time for you to decide what you wanted to be and what you wanted do.  Now, suddenly it seems, you are ending your high school career and people are again asking you, “What are you going to do?”  “What comes next?” is a BIG question – and being a Super Hero is a less likely career option.</p>

<!--more-->


<p>For some, the path is clear – high school to post-secondary to career apprenticeship and employment.  The challenges along this path are getting strong enough grades to be accepted into quota faculties and elite training centres and qualifying for as many scholarships as possible to pay for the necessary accreditation which comes at graduation time.</p>

<p>For others, the path may not be as straight forward and require a more “experiential” approach.  The challenges become based on everyday decisions and immediate circumstances.  Questions such as “Am I qualified to do this job?”, “Do I have the physical and mental stamina to be a success at this?”, “What are the future opportunities for me in this employment setting?”.</p>

<p>Whether or not you know “What comes next?”, one thing is for certain.  You need to keep as many doors to opportunity open as possible.  You need strong grades on your diploma exams so you can confidently apply to the post-secondary institution of your choice or be considered for the apprenticeship position in the newest “disruptor” industry.</p>

<p>During these last few months of the school year, give it all you’ve got!  Check out the many products and services available from <a href="http://www.diplomax.ca">DIPLOMAX.ca</a> to help you get the best grades possible.  You can choose face-to-face sessions, video review sessions, electronic study notes and video support – or any combination!  This is as close to “custom -made studying materials” as is possible.  You can check out the web site <a href="http://www.diplomax.ca">DIPLOMAX.ca</a> for more information. Just remember – “What comes next?” is up to you!</p>

<p><a href="http://www.diplomax.ca">DIPLOMAX.ca</a>
Year-long Support to Classroom Learning.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Second Semester Study Options]]></title>
    <link href="http://blog.diplomax.ca//second-semester-study-options/"/>
    <updated>2017-04-03T19:26:14-06:00</updated>
    <id>http://blog.diplomax.ca//second-semester-study-options</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="center" src="/images/coffee_book.jpg" title="iPrep" ></p>

<p>The new semester is now underway!  We are pleased to remind you that <a href="http://www.diplomax.ca">DIPLOMAX.ca</a> is now accepting registrations for the June <strong>DIPLOMAX In-Class</strong> sessions.  Check out the schedule and register early to secure a spot in the class and session of your choice. Remember – as soon as you complete your registration, you can immediately start to use the Instructor’s Study Notes package to support your classroom instruction.</p>

<!--more-->


<p></p>

<p>If you are not able to attend the DIPLOMAX In-Class sessions, check out the <strong>DIPLOMAX On-Line</strong> sessions and the <strong>iPrep Plus Electronic Study Notes and Video Support</strong> resources.  DIPLOMAX On-Line provides you with a complete video review of the course content – just like the DIPLOMAX In-Class session.  And, you receive a complimentary copy of the Instructor’s Study Notes to download or print.  It’s like being at the session only you can access the video review whenever you want and replay the instruction as many times as you want.  There is no need to download the video review.  You can stream the review on any of your devices.</p>

<p>The <strong>iPrep Plus Electronic Study Notes and Video Support</strong> resources offer you a completely different form of course review than either the DIPLOMAX In-Class or On-Line course review.  The Electronic Study Notes are color-coded to provide you with hints and reminders about various topics and strategies as you work your way through the subject material.  There are 10, short, 8-10 minute videos which focus on the most challenging concepts in each course.  Between the study notes and the videos, you have a very comprehensive review package!</p>

<p>Check out the 3-course semester bundle!  It’s an economical way to help you prepare for your diploma exams whether you are writing them in January, April, June, August or November.</p>

<p><a href="http://www.diplomax.ca">DIPLOMAX.ca</a>
Year-long Support to Classroom Learning.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Strong Finish or a New Start?]]></title>
    <link href="http://blog.diplomax.ca//a-strong-finish-or-a-new-start/"/>
    <updated>2017-01-04T22:57:41-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://blog.diplomax.ca//a-strong-finish-or-a-new-start</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="center" src="/images/happy_new_year.png" title="iPrep" ></p>

<p>Whether you want to finish your first semester with a strong showing or start 2017 with a new self-
assured manner, you can do BOTH by acing your diploma exams!! There is no better feeling than
knowing you are well-prepared and ready to <strong>give it your all</strong> as you write your final test in your course
– the <strong>DIPLOMA EXAM</strong>!! Your grades on each exam combined with your school grades will affect
applications to post-secondary institutions, opportunities to secure scholarships, and employment
opportunities.</p>

<!--more-->


<p></p>

<p>As the first semester of your senior year in high school is coming to an end, be sure you end with a
strong finish! Enroll in a two-day diploma prep class offered by <a href="http://www.diplomax.ca">DIPLOMAX.ca</a>. Check out the many
weekend classes that are offered this January at <a href="http://www.diplomax.ca">DIPLOMAX.ca</a> <em>Be prepared – don’t be sorry</em>!</p>

<p>Check out <a href="http://www.diplomax.ca">DIPLOMAX.ca</a> for the schedule of review sessions, FAQs, facility photos, arriving for the first class, and to register in the class of your choice.  Don’t delay as space is limited!</p>

<p><a href="http://www.diplomax.ca">DIPLOMAX.ca</a>
Year-long Support to Classroom Learning.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[iPrep Plus – Electronic Study Notes and Video Support]]></title>
    <link href="http://blog.diplomax.ca//iprep-plus-electronic-study-notes-and-video-support/"/>
    <updated>2016-12-18T10:14:00-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://blog.diplomax.ca//iprep-plus-electronic-study-notes-and-video-support</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="center" src="/images/iprep.png" title="iPrep" ></p>

<p>The <strong>iPrep Plus Electronic Study Notes and Video Support</strong> resources are unique!  The resources are an electronic resource package that can be downloaded to a personal device or printed and used at home.  They combine comprehensive study notes with short videos to help you independently review course content and clarify understanding.</p>

<!--more-->


<p></p>

<p>The color-coding in the electronic study notes provides hints, reminders, and important things to remember about key concepts.  The electronic study notes can assist you in completing class assignments, reviewing for in-class unit tests and quizzes, and preparing for the diploma exams.  Each resource is from 50-150 pages in length and covers the complete course content.</p>

<p>The resource package also includes <em>10 Support Videos</em> designed to support classroom instruction and learning.  Each video is approximately 8 to 12 minutes in length and focuses on the ‘tough topics’ that students often find challenging.  You can watch the videos as many times as needed to ensure you understand the concept and are confident in your ability to interpret and apply the information in your daily life.</p>

<p>iPrep Plus Electronic Study Notes and Video Support resources are available for Biology 30, Chemistry 30, English 30-1, Math 30-1, Math 30-2, Physics 30, Science 30, and Social Studies 30-1.  These resources provide <em>year-long support</em> for approximately the same cost of one hour of traditional tutoring!  You can access them anytime, anywhere, and on any device.  Use the Electronic Study Notes and Video Support resources to help you achieve strong grades at the end of the semester and on the diploma exams!</p>

<p>Check out <a href="http://www.diplomax.ca">DIPLOMAX.ca</a>for the schedule of review sessions, FAQs, facility photos, arriving for the first class, and to register in the class of your choice.  Don’t delay as space is limited!</p>

<p><a href="http://www.diplomax.ca">DIPLOMAX.ca</a>
Year-long Support to Classroom Learning.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
