<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Diplomax | Diplomax]]></title>
  <link href="http://blog.diplomax.ca//blog/categories/diplomax/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://blog.diplomax.ca//"/>
  <updated>2016-11-03T22:47:45-06:00</updated>
  <id>http://blog.diplomax.ca//</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Diplomax]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[DIPLOMAX In-Class – the Tradition Continues]]></title>
    <link href="http://blog.diplomax.ca//diplomax-in-class-the-tradition-continues/"/>
    <updated>2016-11-03T22:09:11-06:00</updated>
    <id>http://blog.diplomax.ca//diplomax-in-class-the-tradition-continues</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="center" src="/images/blog-nov-3.png" title="Question" ></p>

<p>Tutorial and diploma prep classes have long been offering services to students preparing to write the January and June provincial diploma exams.  For Edmonton and area students, DIPLOMAX In-Class is offering face-to-face, diploma prep review sessions in Biology 30, Chemistry 30, English 30-1, Math 30-1, Math 30-2, Physics 30, Science 30, and Social 30-1.  The comprehensive review sessions in each subject are scheduled from 9:00 am to 5:00 pm on Saturday and Sunday. The classes are held at the University of Alberta Edmonton Campus.  The two-day format makes it easier for students who work or are travelling from surrounding areas to participate in the review sessions.</p>

<!--more-->


<p></p>

<p>Experienced instructors, with a reputation for getting exceptional results with their students, take you through a comprehensive review of the course curriculum and provide you with tips and strategies for writing the diploma exams.  By working through sample questions, you become familiar with the question formats commonly used to test your understanding and the errors students typically make in their responses.  The bonus is you are able to download or print a personal copy of the Instructor’s Study Notes as soon as you complete your registration!  Having the Study Notes available to you immediately gives you more time for review and addressing any course concepts you find particularly challenging.</p>

<p>Check out <a href="http://www.diplomax.ca">DIPLOMAX.ca</a>for the schedule of review sessions, FAQs, facility photos, arriving for the first class, and to register in the class of your choice.  Don’t delay as space is limited!</p>

<p><a href="http://www.diplomax.ca">DIPLOMAX.ca</a>
Year-long Support to Classroom Learning.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[PRESS RELEASE – PROVINCE-WIDE LAUNCH of DIPLOMAX.CA]]></title>
    <link href="http://blog.diplomax.ca//press-release-province-wide-launch-of-diplomax-dot-ca/"/>
    <updated>2016-10-17T21:21:43-06:00</updated>
    <id>http://blog.diplomax.ca//press-release-province-wide-launch-of-diplomax-dot-ca</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="center" src="/images/DIPLOMAX.CA.png" title="Question" ></p>

<p>Writing any diploma exams this year?  Looking for face-to-face help to prepare for the January or June diplomas?  DIPLOMAX In-Class has it for Edmonton and areas students!  Don’t live close enough to Edmonton to participate?  Don’t worry!  DIPLOMAX On-Line is for you!  It is a comprehensive VIDEO REVIEW that comes with a complimentary copy of the Instructor’s Study Notes.  Looking for something that you can use all year long with class assignments, quizzes and unit tests?  iPrep Plus has just what you are looking for!  Use the electronic study notes with video support for the 10 toughest topics!</p>

<!--more-->


<p></p>

<p><a href="http://www.diplomax.ca">DIPLOMAX.ca</a> is an amazing new service that has the support you need to help you do your best on the diploma exams and your in-class assignments - no matter where you live in Alberta.  As the competition for scholarships and entrance to quota faculties becomes more challenging, it is increasingly important to achieve the highest scores possible on your year-end grades and the provincial diploma exams.  <a href="http://www.diplomax.ca">DIPLOMAX.ca</a> has products and services designed to help you do just that!</p>

<p>Recognizing the need for quality, affordable resources that students can access anytime, anywhere, and on any device, Noel Kunst, noted educator, former assistant superintendent, and now independent consultant, put together a team of experienced and talented instructors to create “what students need” to support their classroom learning and maximize their achievement results.  If you, or anyone you know, is taking Biology 30, Chemistry 30, English 30-1, Math 30-1, Math 30-2, Physics 30, Science 30, or Social 30-1, have them visit www.diplomax.ca to find out more about the new products and services developed especially for them!  Check your school counselling department for printed information about the great products and services available to you through DIPLOMAX.ca!</p>

<p><a href="http://www.diplomax.ca">DIPLOMAX.ca</a>
Year-long Support to Classroom Learning.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Study Schedules – Long-term, Short-term, and PANIC!]]></title>
    <link href="http://blog.diplomax.ca//study-schedules-long-term/"/>
    <updated>2016-05-08T12:17:05-06:00</updated>
    <id>http://blog.diplomax.ca//study-schedules-long-term</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="center" src="/images/grades.jpg" title="&ldquo;Girls with grades&rdquo;" ></p>

<p>Have you ever read the story of <em>The Hare and the Tortoise?</em>  It is a delightful children’s story of a race between two animal friends who each are confident of their ability to win a race.  The Hare sets off to a speedy start and covers a significant amount of territory before deciding he has enough of a head start on the Tortoise that he can stop for a rest.  He settles under a shady tree and enjoys a nap, confident that he can sprint to the finish line well before the Tortoise can catch up to him.</p>

<!--more-->


<p></p>

<p>The Tortoise leaves the start line slowly plodding along the race path.  Though not a flashy racer, he keeps a steady pace and remains focused on getting to the finish line.  He passes the sleeping Hare and soon sees the finish line looming in the distance.  As the Tortoise is within steps of crossing the finish line and winning the race, the Hare wakes up.  He realizes he needs to make a spirited sprint to overtake the Tortoise.  Unfortunately, the Hare’s panicked dash for the finish line is “too little too late”.  The Tortoise, although a long shot, wins the race and the brazen, confident Hare is left humiliated and searching for an explanation for his loss.</p>

<p>There are many analogies that can be drawn between the race strategies of the story characters and long-term, short-term, and panic study schedules.</p>

<p><strong>Long-term Study Schedules</strong> generally are implemented well in advance of exam time and require you to set aside regular study time on an on-going basis.  Like the Tortoise a slow and steady approach helps to win the race.  The advantage of a long-term study schedule is that once you establish your study routine, it is quite easy to maintain – and shorter, regular periods of study give you the most benefit!</p>

<p><strong>Short-term Study Schedules</strong> are often implemented several days or weeks before an exam and require you to prioritize the time you spend on each topic or concept.  It may be difficult to find a “starting point”.  Do you focus on the things that are most important in the subject or on the concepts that are most challenging to you? Like the Hare, your focus may change before the end of the race.  You may skim over content that you feel you have a firm understanding of in favor of focusing on topics that feel less confident about.  Your focus may not be as consistent or as strong as it needs to be for the duration of your study or exam preparation time. The advantage of a short-term study schedule is that you gain a sense of confidence as you “check off” the topics and concepts you feel confident about.</p>

<p><img class="right" src="/images/panic.jpeg" title="&ldquo;Panic&rdquo;" ></p>

<p><strong>Panic Study Schedules</strong> usually happen “the night before” the exam – when you realize that you do not have enough time to adequately prepare for your exam.  Although this study schedule requires the least amount of time commitment, it rarely allows you to achieve your potential.  Like the Hare, leaving too much to the end makes it impossible to finish what needs to be done.  However, any effort is better than doing nothing.</p>

<p>To achieve the grades you want requires effort on your part.  A long-term study schedule gives you the best chance for success.  A short-term study schedule may work well in a course where you have a strong understanding of the concepts.  A Panic Study Schedule is better than not studying at all but may not help you to achieve your course goals over the semester or school year.</p>

<p><strong>Does your study strategy resemble the race strategy of the Hare or the Tortoise?</strong></p>

<p>Check out the web site <a href="http://www.iPrepPlus.com">www.iPrepPlus.com</a> for the <strong>introductory price offer</strong> and many features!</p>

<p>If you are serious about your academic success – <strong>iPrep Plus</strong> and <strong>Diplomax</strong> are here to help you!</p>

<p><em>iPrep Plus – Year-long Support for Classroom Learning</em>
More than you imagined for less than you expected – electronic study notes and video support for tough topics!
<a href="http://www.iPrepPlus.com">www.iPrepPlus.com</a></p>

<p><em>Diplomax – Your Premier Choice for Diploma Prep</em>
For Edmonton and area face-to-face review classes in January and June check  <a href="http://www.primetimelearning.ca">www.primetimelearning.ca</a></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
