<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Math 30-2 | Diplomax]]></title>
  <link href="http://blog.diplomax.ca//blog/categories/math-30-2/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://blog.diplomax.ca//"/>
  <updated>2017-04-24T23:46:19-06:00</updated>
  <id>http://blog.diplomax.ca//</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Diplomax]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[iPrep Plus Gives Students ‘Leg Up’]]></title>
    <link href="http://blog.diplomax.ca//iprep-plus-gives-students-leg-up/"/>
    <updated>2016-05-17T17:42:35-06:00</updated>
    <id>http://blog.diplomax.ca//iprep-plus-gives-students-leg-up</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="center" src="/images/student_edge.jpg" title="Question" ></p>

<p>High-stakes diploma exams in January and June are always a challenge for grade 12 students.   These provincial exams count for 30% of your final grade but the other 70% comes from your efforts on school-based assessments.</p>

<!--more-->


<p></p>

<p>For a variety of reasons, it is becoming more and more common for students to seek assistance beyond the classroom in preparing for the diploma exams.  Entrance requirements for many post-secondary institutions have increased over the years so you need better grades to gain admittance.  The competition is extremely keen for faculties that have quotas and only take the top echelon of applicants.  Then there are the numerous scholarships available for the students who have the top grades!</p>

<p>Teachers work very diligently to get through the extensive, mandated curriculum but often find little time left in the semester for completing a review of the course content.  Students are now looking to external sources for the comprehensive review that will give them the “edge” they need to boost their marks – and open the doors to the future they are seeking.</p>

<p>iPrep Plus gives you exactly what you are looking for! The comprehensive Electronic Study Notes and Video Support resource packages for English 30-1, Biology 30, Chemistry 30, Math 30-1, Math 30-2, Physics 30, Science 30 and Social Studies 30-1 can be used at home to support your classroom learning.  You are provided with a comprehensive course review, video support for the “tough topics”, tips and strategies for writing exams, suggestions for handling exam anxiety, calculator tricks, and effective study hints.</p>

<p>Visit the iPrep Plus web site at www.iPrepPlus.com to watch a “video sampler”, review the course descriptions, and for more information about the introductory price which available for a limited time!</p>

<p>Check out the web site <a href="http://www.iPrepPlus.com">www.iPrepPlus.com</a> for the <strong>introductory price offer</strong> and many features!</p>

<p>If you are serious about your academic success – <strong>iPrep Plus</strong> and <strong>Diplomax</strong> are here to help you!</p>

<p><em>iPrep Plus – Year-long Support for Classroom Learning</em>
More than you imagined for less than you expected – electronic study notes and video support for tough topics!
<a href="http://www.iPrepPlus.com">www.iPrepPlus.com</a></p>

<p><em>Diplomax – Your Premier Choice for Diploma Prep</em>
For Edmonton and area face-to-face review classes in January and June check  <a href="http://www.primetimelearning.ca">www.primetimelearning.ca</a></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Math 30-2 — Sample Question and Solution for Set Theory #3]]></title>
    <link href="http://blog.diplomax.ca//math-30-2-sample-question-and-solution-for-set-theory-number-3/"/>
    <updated>2016-05-15T13:26:04-06:00</updated>
    <id>http://blog.diplomax.ca//math-30-2-sample-question-and-solution-for-set-theory-number-3</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Try this sample question to gauge your diploma preparation for Math 30-2!</p>

<p><img class="center" src="/images/question_SetTheory_1.png" title="Question" ></p>

<!--more-->


<p></p>

<p><img class="center" src="/images/question_SetTheory_2.png" title="Question" ></p>

<p><img class="center" src="/images/question_SetTheory_3.png" title="Question" ></p>

<p>Check out the web site <a href="http://www.iPrepPlus.com">www.iPrepPlus.com</a> for the <strong>introductory price offer</strong> and many features!</p>

<p>If you are serious about your academic success – <strong>iPrep Plus</strong> and <strong>Diplomax</strong> are here to help you!</p>

<p><em>iPrep Plus – Year-long Support for Classroom Learning</em>
More than you imagined for less than you expected – electronic study notes and video support for tough topics!
<a href="http://www.iPrepPlus.com">www.iPrepPlus.com</a></p>

<p><em>Diplomax – Your Premier Choice for Diploma Prep</em>
For Edmonton and area face-to-face review classes in January and June check  <a href="http://www.primetimelearning.ca">www.primetimelearning.ca</a></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Study Schedules – Long-term, Short-term, and PANIC!]]></title>
    <link href="http://blog.diplomax.ca//study-schedules-long-term/"/>
    <updated>2016-05-08T12:17:05-06:00</updated>
    <id>http://blog.diplomax.ca//study-schedules-long-term</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="center" src="/images/grades.jpg" title="&ldquo;Girls with grades&rdquo;" ></p>

<p>Have you ever read the story of <em>The Hare and the Tortoise?</em>  It is a delightful children’s story of a race between two animal friends who each are confident of their ability to win a race.  The Hare sets off to a speedy start and covers a significant amount of territory before deciding he has enough of a head start on the Tortoise that he can stop for a rest.  He settles under a shady tree and enjoys a nap, confident that he can sprint to the finish line well before the Tortoise can catch up to him.</p>

<!--more-->


<p></p>

<p>The Tortoise leaves the start line slowly plodding along the race path.  Though not a flashy racer, he keeps a steady pace and remains focused on getting to the finish line.  He passes the sleeping Hare and soon sees the finish line looming in the distance.  As the Tortoise is within steps of crossing the finish line and winning the race, the Hare wakes up.  He realizes he needs to make a spirited sprint to overtake the Tortoise.  Unfortunately, the Hare’s panicked dash for the finish line is “too little too late”.  The Tortoise, although a long shot, wins the race and the brazen, confident Hare is left humiliated and searching for an explanation for his loss.</p>

<p>There are many analogies that can be drawn between the race strategies of the story characters and long-term, short-term, and panic study schedules.</p>

<p><strong>Long-term Study Schedules</strong> generally are implemented well in advance of exam time and require you to set aside regular study time on an on-going basis.  Like the Tortoise a slow and steady approach helps to win the race.  The advantage of a long-term study schedule is that once you establish your study routine, it is quite easy to maintain – and shorter, regular periods of study give you the most benefit!</p>

<p><strong>Short-term Study Schedules</strong> are often implemented several days or weeks before an exam and require you to prioritize the time you spend on each topic or concept.  It may be difficult to find a “starting point”.  Do you focus on the things that are most important in the subject or on the concepts that are most challenging to you? Like the Hare, your focus may change before the end of the race.  You may skim over content that you feel you have a firm understanding of in favor of focusing on topics that feel less confident about.  Your focus may not be as consistent or as strong as it needs to be for the duration of your study or exam preparation time. The advantage of a short-term study schedule is that you gain a sense of confidence as you “check off” the topics and concepts you feel confident about.</p>

<p><img class="right" src="/images/panic.jpeg" title="&ldquo;Panic&rdquo;" ></p>

<p><strong>Panic Study Schedules</strong> usually happen “the night before” the exam – when you realize that you do not have enough time to adequately prepare for your exam.  Although this study schedule requires the least amount of time commitment, it rarely allows you to achieve your potential.  Like the Hare, leaving too much to the end makes it impossible to finish what needs to be done.  However, any effort is better than doing nothing.</p>

<p>To achieve the grades you want requires effort on your part.  A long-term study schedule gives you the best chance for success.  A short-term study schedule may work well in a course where you have a strong understanding of the concepts.  A Panic Study Schedule is better than not studying at all but may not help you to achieve your course goals over the semester or school year.</p>

<p><strong>Does your study strategy resemble the race strategy of the Hare or the Tortoise?</strong></p>

<p>Check out the web site <a href="http://www.iPrepPlus.com">www.iPrepPlus.com</a> for the <strong>introductory price offer</strong> and many features!</p>

<p>If you are serious about your academic success – <strong>iPrep Plus</strong> and <strong>Diplomax</strong> are here to help you!</p>

<p><em>iPrep Plus – Year-long Support for Classroom Learning</em>
More than you imagined for less than you expected – electronic study notes and video support for tough topics!
<a href="http://www.iPrepPlus.com">www.iPrepPlus.com</a></p>

<p><em>Diplomax – Your Premier Choice for Diploma Prep</em>
For Edmonton and area face-to-face review classes in January and June check  <a href="http://www.primetimelearning.ca">www.primetimelearning.ca</a></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
