<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Primetime | Diplomax]]></title>
  <link href="http://blog.diplomax.ca//blog/categories/primetime/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://blog.diplomax.ca//"/>
  <updated>2018-05-07T19:33:17-06:00</updated>
  <id>http://blog.diplomax.ca//</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Diplomax]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Diploma Prep Study Options]]></title>
    <link href="http://blog.diplomax.ca//diploma-prep-study-options/"/>
    <updated>2018-05-07T19:26:47-06:00</updated>
    <id>http://blog.diplomax.ca//diploma-prep-study-options</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="center" src="/images/blog_4.jpg" title="teacher" ></p>

<p>The new semester is now underway!  We are pleased to remind you that <strong><a href="http://www.diplomax.ca">DIPLOMAX.ca</a></strong>  is now accepting registrations for the June <strong>DIPLOMAX In-Class</strong> sessions.  Check out the schedule and register early to secure a spot in the class and session of your choice. Remember – as soon as you complete your registration, you can immediately start to use the Instructor’s Study Notes package to support your classroom instruction.</p>

<!--more-->


<p>If you are not able to attend the <strong><a href="http://www.diplomax.ca">DIPLOMAX</a></strong>  In-Class sessions, check out the DIPLOMAX On-Line sessions and the <strong>iPrep Plus Electronic Study Notes and Video Support</strong> resources.  <strong>DIPLOMAX On-Line</strong> provides you with a complete video review of the course content – just like the <strong><a href="http://www.diplomax.ca">DIPLOMAX</a></strong>  In-Class session.  And, you receive a complimentary copy of the Instructor’s Study Notes to download or print.  It’s like being at the session only you can access the video review whenever you want and replay the instruction as many times as you want.  There is no need to download the video review.  You can stream the review on any of your devices.</p>

<p>The <strong>iPrep Plus Electronic Study Notes and Video Support</strong> resources offer you a completely different form of course review than either the DIPLOMAX In-Class or On-Line course review.  The Electronic Study Notes are color-coded to provide you with hints and reminders about various topics and strategies as you work your way through the subject material.  There are 10, short, 8-10 minute videos which focus on the most challenging concepts in each course.  Between the study notes and the videos, you have a very comprehensive review package!</p>

<p>Check out the 3-course semester bundle!  It’s an economical way to help you prepare for your diploma exams whether you are writing them in January, April, June, August or November.</p>

<p><a href="http://www.diplomax.ca">DIPLOMAX.ca</a>
Year-long Support to Classroom Learning.</p>

<p><strong>Not only Authors BUT Exceptional Educators</strong></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Not Only Authors but Exceptional Educators]]></title>
    <link href="http://blog.diplomax.ca//not-only-authors-but-exceptional-educators/"/>
    <updated>2017-05-23T18:45:58-06:00</updated>
    <id>http://blog.diplomax.ca//not-only-authors-but-exceptional-educators</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="center" src="/images/teacher.jpg" title="teacher" ></p>

<p>When there are so many self-help books on the market, how many can you buy, and how do you know which ones will actually be useful?  The answer is easy!  Look for the educational resources that have been developed by experienced educators who have a strong reputation for helping student achieve remarkable results.</p>

<!--more-->


<p>All the <strong><a href="http://www.diplomax.ca">DIPLOMAX.ca</a></strong> and <strong><em>iPrep Plus</em></strong> Electronic Study Notes and Video Support resource packages have been created by actual teachers who understand what you need to know to be successful in the subject.  The educator/authors have provided a comprehensive overview of the Grade 12 course material in language you can understand, included tips for reviewing, and filmed video support clips on the “tough topics” that seem to present challenges to students.</p>

<p>The veteran educators use their knowledge of curriculum, instruction, assessment, expertise, extensive experiences in developing diploma exam questions and marking provincial exams, and their passion for the subject to create strong resources.  Each product focuses on concepts and skills you need to master to maximize your results!</p>

<p>Many of the authors are provincial nominees and Teacher of Excellence Award winners.  Visit the <strong><a href="http://www.diplomax.ca">DIPLOMAX</a> </strong>web site www.diplomax.ca to meet our team of authors and educators.  You may even recognize some of these outstanding educators!</p>

<p><a href="http://www.diplomax.ca">DIPLOMAX.ca</a>
Year-long Support to Classroom Learning.</p>

<p><strong>Not only Authors BUT Exceptional Educators</strong></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Finding Help to Support Classroom Learning]]></title>
    <link href="http://blog.diplomax.ca//finding-help-to-support-classroom-learning/"/>
    <updated>2017-04-22T20:43:29-06:00</updated>
    <id>http://blog.diplomax.ca//finding-help-to-support-classroom-learning</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="center" src="/images/sweat-confusion.jpg" title="confused" ></p>

<p>How many times have you left class and thought <em>“None of this makes sense to me!</em>”?  How many times have you felt your confidence drain away as your tried to complete a major assignment?  How many times have you tried unsuccessfully to apply the formulas you thought you understood in class, to your homework questions to find that you couldn’t remember the steps in the process?  Nothing is more frustrating than trying your hardest to do well but not having the extra help at home when you need it most!</p>

<!--more-->


<p><a href="http://www.diplomax.ca">DIPLOMAX.ca</a> has just what you are looking for!  The <strong>iPrep Plus Electronic Study Notes and Video Support</strong>  resources are unique.  Each resource combines a comprehensive study notes package with short videos on the most challenging course topics to provide you a means of independently reviewing your course content and clarifying your understanding.  You can use the materials to help you with homework assignments, prepare for unit tests and quizzes, completing projects, and reviewing classroom learning.  Watch the videos as many time as needed to ensure you understand the concept.  It’s like having a personal tutor on stand-by while you do your studying at home.</p>

<p>Still not certain if the <strong>iPrep Plus Electronic Study Notes and Video Support</strong> resources will meet your needs?  Then visit www.diplomax.ca  Choose your subject – Biology 30, Chemistry 30, English 30-1, Math 30-1, Math 30-2, Physics 30, Science 30, or Social 30-1.  Watch some of the sample videos and review the sample pages from the resources.  Check out the color-coding in the resources intended to give you hints and help you to remember key strategies and concepts.  Each resource is approximately 50-150 pages that you can download or print.  Each subject has 10 videos of 8-10 minutes in length that focus on the most challenging concepts of the course.</p>

<p>The <strong>iPrep Plus Electronic Study Notes and Video Support</strong> resources provide you with year-long support for approximately the same cost as one hour of traditional tutoring.  When you need the extra help at home, these resources give you the necessary support.  What are you waiting for?  Check it out!</p>

<p><a href="http://www.diplomax.ca">DIPLOMAX.ca</a>
Year-long Support to Classroom Learning.
<strong>Not only Authors BUT Exceptional Educators</strong></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Comes Next?]]></title>
    <link href="http://blog.diplomax.ca//what-comes-next/"/>
    <updated>2017-04-12T18:06:00-06:00</updated>
    <id>http://blog.diplomax.ca//what-comes-next</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="center" src="/images/what_comes_next.jpg" title="what_comes_next" ></p>

<p>Remember when you started school and everyone asked you what you wanted to be when you grew up?  It seemed like there were endless possibilities and lots of time for you to decide what you wanted to be and what you wanted do.  Now, suddenly it seems, you are ending your high school career and people are again asking you, “What are you going to do?”  “What comes next?” is a BIG question – and being a Super Hero is a less likely career option.</p>

<!--more-->


<p>For some, the path is clear – high school to post-secondary to career apprenticeship and employment.  The challenges along this path are getting strong enough grades to be accepted into quota faculties and elite training centres and qualifying for as many scholarships as possible to pay for the necessary accreditation which comes at graduation time.</p>

<p>For others, the path may not be as straight forward and require a more “experiential” approach.  The challenges become based on everyday decisions and immediate circumstances.  Questions such as “Am I qualified to do this job?”, “Do I have the physical and mental stamina to be a success at this?”, “What are the future opportunities for me in this employment setting?”.</p>

<p>Whether or not you know “What comes next?”, one thing is for certain.  You need to keep as many doors to opportunity open as possible.  You need strong grades on your diploma exams so you can confidently apply to the post-secondary institution of your choice or be considered for the apprenticeship position in the newest “disruptor” industry.</p>

<p>During these last few months of the school year, give it all you’ve got!  Check out the many products and services available from <a href="http://www.diplomax.ca">DIPLOMAX.ca</a> to help you get the best grades possible.  You can choose face-to-face sessions, video review sessions, electronic study notes and video support – or any combination!  This is as close to “custom -made studying materials” as is possible.  You can check out the web site <a href="http://www.diplomax.ca">DIPLOMAX.ca</a> for more information. Just remember – “What comes next?” is up to you!</p>

<p><a href="http://www.diplomax.ca">DIPLOMAX.ca</a>
Year-long Support to Classroom Learning.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Second Semester Study Options]]></title>
    <link href="http://blog.diplomax.ca//second-semester-study-options/"/>
    <updated>2017-04-03T19:26:14-06:00</updated>
    <id>http://blog.diplomax.ca//second-semester-study-options</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="center" src="/images/coffee_book.jpg" title="iPrep" ></p>

<p>The new semester is now underway!  We are pleased to remind you that <a href="http://www.diplomax.ca">DIPLOMAX.ca</a> is now accepting registrations for the June <strong>DIPLOMAX In-Class</strong> sessions.  Check out the schedule and register early to secure a spot in the class and session of your choice. Remember – as soon as you complete your registration, you can immediately start to use the Instructor’s Study Notes package to support your classroom instruction.</p>

<!--more-->


<p></p>

<p>If you are not able to attend the DIPLOMAX In-Class sessions, check out the <strong>DIPLOMAX On-Line</strong> sessions and the <strong>iPrep Plus Electronic Study Notes and Video Support</strong> resources.  DIPLOMAX On-Line provides you with a complete video review of the course content – just like the DIPLOMAX In-Class session.  And, you receive a complimentary copy of the Instructor’s Study Notes to download or print.  It’s like being at the session only you can access the video review whenever you want and replay the instruction as many times as you want.  There is no need to download the video review.  You can stream the review on any of your devices.</p>

<p>The <strong>iPrep Plus Electronic Study Notes and Video Support</strong> resources offer you a completely different form of course review than either the DIPLOMAX In-Class or On-Line course review.  The Electronic Study Notes are color-coded to provide you with hints and reminders about various topics and strategies as you work your way through the subject material.  There are 10, short, 8-10 minute videos which focus on the most challenging concepts in each course.  Between the study notes and the videos, you have a very comprehensive review package!</p>

<p>Check out the 3-course semester bundle!  It’s an economical way to help you prepare for your diploma exams whether you are writing them in January, April, June, August or November.</p>

<p><a href="http://www.diplomax.ca">DIPLOMAX.ca</a>
Year-long Support to Classroom Learning.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
