<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Primetime | Diplomax]]></title>
  <link href="http://blog.diplomax.ca//blog/categories/primetime/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://blog.diplomax.ca//"/>
  <updated>2016-12-18T10:33:21-07:00</updated>
  <id>http://blog.diplomax.ca//</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Diplomax]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[iPrep Plus – Electronic Study Notes and Video Support]]></title>
    <link href="http://blog.diplomax.ca//iprep-plus-electronic-study-notes-and-video-support/"/>
    <updated>2016-12-18T10:14:00-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://blog.diplomax.ca//iprep-plus-electronic-study-notes-and-video-support</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="center" src="/images/iprep.png" title="iPrep" ></p>

<p>The <strong>iPrep Plus Electronic Study Notes and Video Support</strong> resources are unique!  The resources are an electronic resource package that can be downloaded to a personal device or printed and used at home.  They combine comprehensive study notes with short videos to help you independently review course content and clarify understanding.</p>

<!--more-->


<p></p>

<p>The color-coding in the electronic study notes provides hints, reminders, and important things to remember about key concepts.  The electronic study notes can assist you in completing class assignments, reviewing for in-class unit tests and quizzes, and preparing for the diploma exams.  Each resource is from 50-150 pages in length and covers the complete course content.</p>

<p>The resource package also includes <em>10 Support Videos</em> designed to support classroom instruction and learning.  Each video is approximately 8 to 12 minutes in length and focuses on the ‘tough topics’ that students often find challenging.  You can watch the videos as many times as needed to ensure you understand the concept and are confident in your ability to interpret and apply the information in your daily life.</p>

<p>iPrep Plus Electronic Study Notes and Video Support resources are available for Biology 30, Chemistry 30, English 30-1, Math 30-1, Math 30-2, Physics 30, Science 30, and Social Studies 30-1.  These resources provide <em>year-long support</em> for approximately the same cost of one hour of traditional tutoring!  You can access them anytime, anywhere, and on any device.  Use the Electronic Study Notes and Video Support resources to help you achieve strong grades at the end of the semester and on the diploma exams!</p>

<p>Check out <a href="http://www.diplomax.ca">DIPLOMAX.ca</a>for the schedule of review sessions, FAQs, facility photos, arriving for the first class, and to register in the class of your choice.  Don’t delay as space is limited!</p>

<p><a href="http://www.diplomax.ca">DIPLOMAX.ca</a>
Year-long Support to Classroom Learning.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[DIPLOMAX In-Class – the Tradition Continues]]></title>
    <link href="http://blog.diplomax.ca//diplomax-in-class-the-tradition-continues/"/>
    <updated>2016-11-03T22:09:11-06:00</updated>
    <id>http://blog.diplomax.ca//diplomax-in-class-the-tradition-continues</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="center" src="/images/blog-nov-3.png" title="Question" ></p>

<p>Tutorial and diploma prep classes have long been offering services to students preparing to write the January and June provincial diploma exams.  For Edmonton and area students, DIPLOMAX In-Class is offering face-to-face, diploma prep review sessions in Biology 30, Chemistry 30, English 30-1, Math 30-1, Math 30-2, Physics 30, Science 30, and Social 30-1.  The comprehensive review sessions in each subject are scheduled from 9:00 am to 5:00 pm on Saturday and Sunday. The classes are held at the University of Alberta Edmonton Campus.  The two-day format makes it easier for students who work or are travelling from surrounding areas to participate in the review sessions.</p>

<!--more-->


<p></p>

<p>Experienced instructors, with a reputation for getting exceptional results with their students, take you through a comprehensive review of the course curriculum and provide you with tips and strategies for writing the diploma exams.  By working through sample questions, you become familiar with the question formats commonly used to test your understanding and the errors students typically make in their responses.  The bonus is you are able to download or print a personal copy of the Instructor’s Study Notes as soon as you complete your registration!  Having the Study Notes available to you immediately gives you more time for review and addressing any course concepts you find particularly challenging.</p>

<p>Check out <a href="http://www.diplomax.ca">DIPLOMAX.ca</a>for the schedule of review sessions, FAQs, facility photos, arriving for the first class, and to register in the class of your choice.  Don’t delay as space is limited!</p>

<p><a href="http://www.diplomax.ca">DIPLOMAX.ca</a>
Year-long Support to Classroom Learning.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[PRESS RELEASE – PROVINCE-WIDE LAUNCH of DIPLOMAX.CA]]></title>
    <link href="http://blog.diplomax.ca//press-release-province-wide-launch-of-diplomax-dot-ca/"/>
    <updated>2016-10-17T21:21:43-06:00</updated>
    <id>http://blog.diplomax.ca//press-release-province-wide-launch-of-diplomax-dot-ca</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="center" src="/images/DIPLOMAX.CA.png" title="Question" ></p>

<p>Writing any diploma exams this year?  Looking for face-to-face help to prepare for the January or June diplomas?  DIPLOMAX In-Class has it for Edmonton and areas students!  Don’t live close enough to Edmonton to participate?  Don’t worry!  DIPLOMAX On-Line is for you!  It is a comprehensive VIDEO REVIEW that comes with a complimentary copy of the Instructor’s Study Notes.  Looking for something that you can use all year long with class assignments, quizzes and unit tests?  iPrep Plus has just what you are looking for!  Use the electronic study notes with video support for the 10 toughest topics!</p>

<!--more-->


<p></p>

<p><a href="http://www.diplomax.ca">DIPLOMAX.ca</a> is an amazing new service that has the support you need to help you do your best on the diploma exams and your in-class assignments - no matter where you live in Alberta.  As the competition for scholarships and entrance to quota faculties becomes more challenging, it is increasingly important to achieve the highest scores possible on your year-end grades and the provincial diploma exams.  <a href="http://www.diplomax.ca">DIPLOMAX.ca</a> has products and services designed to help you do just that!</p>

<p>Recognizing the need for quality, affordable resources that students can access anytime, anywhere, and on any device, Noel Kunst, noted educator, former assistant superintendent, and now independent consultant, put together a team of experienced and talented instructors to create “what students need” to support their classroom learning and maximize their achievement results.  If you, or anyone you know, is taking Biology 30, Chemistry 30, English 30-1, Math 30-1, Math 30-2, Physics 30, Science 30, or Social 30-1, have them visit www.diplomax.ca to find out more about the new products and services developed especially for them!  Check your school counselling department for printed information about the great products and services available to you through DIPLOMAX.ca!</p>

<p><a href="http://www.diplomax.ca">DIPLOMAX.ca</a>
Year-long Support to Classroom Learning.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
